{
    "name": "ES_EN",
    "version": "0.1",
    "data": [
      {
          "id": "1",
          "question": "de",
          "solution": "from",
          "additionText": "of"
      },
      {
          "id": "2",
          "question": "la",
          "solution": "the",
          "additionText": "the"
      },
      {
          "id": "3",
          "question": "que",
          "solution": "that",
          "additionText": "which"
      },
      {
          "id": "4",
          "question": "el",
          "solution": "the",
          "additionText": "the"
      },
      {
          "id": "5",
          "question": "en",
          "solution": "in",
          "additionText": "at"
      },
      {
          "id": "6",
          "question": "y",
          "solution": "and",
          "additionText": "y"
      },
      {
          "id": "7",
          "question": "a",
          "solution": "to",
          "additionText": "a"
      },
      {
          "id": "8",
          "question": "los",
          "solution": "the",
          "additionText": "the"
      },
      {
          "id": "9",
          "question": "se",
          "solution": "I know",
          "additionText": "se"
      },
      {
          "id": "10",
          "question": "del",
          "solution": "of the",
          "additionText": "from"
      },
      {
          "id": "11",
          "question": "las",
          "solution": "the",
          "additionText": "the"
      },
      {
          "id": "12",
          "question": "un",
          "solution": "a",
          "additionText": "a"
      },
      {
          "id": "13",
          "question": "por",
          "solution": "by",
          "additionText": "by"
      },
      {
          "id": "14",
          "question": "con",
          "solution": "with",
          "additionText": "with"
      },
      {
          "id": "15",
          "question": "no",
          "solution": "no",
          "additionText": "no"
      },
      {
          "id": "16",
          "question": "una",
          "solution": "a",
          "additionText": "a"
      },
      {
          "id": "17",
          "question": "su",
          "solution": "its",
          "additionText": "your"
      },
      {
          "id": "18",
          "question": "para",
          "solution": "for",
          "additionText": "for"
      },
      {
          "id": "19",
          "question": "es",
          "solution": "is",
          "additionText": "es"
      },
      {
          "id": "20",
          "question": "al",
          "solution": "to the",
          "additionText": "at"
      },
      {
          "id": "21",
          "question": "lo",
          "solution": "it",
          "additionText": "lo"
      },
      {
          "id": "22",
          "question": "como",
          "solution": "What",
          "additionText": "as"
      },
      {
          "id": "23",
          "question": "más",
          "solution": "plus",
          "additionText": "more"
      },
      {
          "id": "24",
          "question": "o",
          "solution": "or",
          "additionText": "o"
      },
      {
          "id": "25",
          "question": "pero",
          "solution": "but",
          "additionText": "but"
      },
      {
          "id": "26",
          "question": "sus",
          "solution": "their",
          "additionText": "your"
      },
      {
          "id": "27",
          "question": "le",
          "solution": "you",
          "additionText": "le"
      },
      {
          "id": "28",
          "question": "ha",
          "solution": "ha",
          "additionText": "has"
      },
      {
          "id": "29",
          "question": "me",
          "solution": "I",
          "additionText": "me"
      },
      {
          "id": "30",
          "question": "si",
          "solution": "Yes",
          "additionText": "if"
      },
      {
          "id": "31",
          "question": "sin",
          "solution": "without",
          "additionText": "without"
      },
      {
          "id": "32",
          "question": "sobre",
          "solution": "on",
          "additionText": "about"
      },
      {
          "id": "33",
          "question": "este",
          "solution": "East",
          "additionText": "this"
      },
      {
          "id": "34",
          "question": "ya",
          "solution": "already",
          "additionText": "already"
      },
      {
          "id": "35",
          "question": "entre",
          "solution": "Come in",
          "additionText": "between"
      },
      {
          "id": "36",
          "question": "cuando",
          "solution": "when",
          "additionText": "when"
      },
      {
          "id": "37",
          "question": "todo",
          "solution": "all",
          "additionText": "all"
      },
      {
          "id": "38",
          "question": "esta",
          "solution": "is",
          "additionText": "is"
      },
      {
          "id": "39",
          "question": "ser",
          "solution": "be",
          "additionText": "be"
      },
      {
          "id": "40",
          "question": "son",
          "solution": "are",
          "additionText": "are"
      },
      {
          "id": "41",
          "question": "dos",
          "solution": "two",
          "additionText": "two"
      },
      {
          "id": "42",
          "question": "también",
          "solution": "too",
          "additionText": "also"
      },
      {
          "id": "43",
          "question": "fue",
          "solution": "it was",
          "additionText": "was"
      },
      {
          "id": "44",
          "question": "había",
          "solution": "there was",
          "additionText": "there was"
      },
      {
          "id": "45",
          "question": "era",
          "solution": "it was",
          "additionText": "was"
      },
      {
          "id": "46",
          "question": "muy",
          "solution": "very",
          "additionText": "very"
      },
      {
          "id": "47",
          "question": "años",
          "solution": "years",
          "additionText": "years"
      },
      {
          "id": "48",
          "question": "hasta",
          "solution": "until",
          "additionText": "to"
      },
      {
          "id": "49",
          "question": "desde",
          "solution": "since",
          "additionText": "since"
      },
      {
          "id": "50",
          "question": "está",
          "solution": "this",
          "additionText": "is"
      },
      {
          "id": "51",
          "question": "mi",
          "solution": "me",
          "additionText": "my"
      },
      {
          "id": "52",
          "question": "porque",
          "solution": "because",
          "additionText": "because"
      },
      {
          "id": "53",
          "question": "qué",
          "solution": "that",
          "additionText": "what"
      },
      {
          "id": "54",
          "question": "sólo",
          "solution": "alone",
          "additionText": "only"
      },
      {
          "id": "55",
          "question": "han",
          "solution": "they have",
          "additionText": "have"
      },
      {
          "id": "56",
          "question": "yo",
          "solution": "I",
          "additionText": "me"
      },
      {
          "id": "57",
          "question": "hay",
          "solution": "there are",
          "additionText": "there is"
      },
      {
          "id": "58",
          "question": "vez",
          "solution": "time",
          "additionText": "time"
      },
      {
          "id": "59",
          "question": "puede",
          "solution": "can",
          "additionText": "can"
      },
      {
          "id": "60",
          "question": "todos",
          "solution": "everybody",
          "additionText": "all"
      },
      {
          "id": "61",
          "question": "así",
          "solution": "So",
          "additionText": "so"
      },
      {
          "id": "62",
          "question": "nos",
          "solution": "us",
          "additionText": "us"
      },
      {
          "id": "63",
          "question": "ni",
          "solution": "neither",
          "additionText": "nor"
      },
      {
          "id": "64",
          "question": "parte",
          "solution": "part",
          "additionText": "part"
      },
      {
          "id": "65",
          "question": "tiene",
          "solution": "It has",
          "additionText": "has"
      },
      {
          "id": "66",
          "question": "él",
          "solution": "he",
          "additionText": "he"
      },
      {
          "id": "67",
          "question": "uno",
          "solution": "one",
          "additionText": "one"
      },
      {
          "id": "68",
          "question": "donde",
          "solution": "where",
          "additionText": "where"
      },
      {
          "id": "69",
          "question": "bien",
          "solution": "all right",
          "additionText": "well"
      },
      {
          "id": "70",
          "question": "tiempo",
          "solution": "weather",
          "additionText": "time"
      },
      {
          "id": "71",
          "question": "mismo",
          "solution": "same",
          "additionText": "itself"
      },
      {
          "id": "72",
          "question": "ese",
          "solution": "that",
          "additionText": "that"
      },
      {
          "id": "73",
          "question": "ahora",
          "solution": "now",
          "additionText": "now"
      },
      {
          "id": "74",
          "question": "cada",
          "solution": "each",
          "additionText": "each"
      },
      {
          "id": "75",
          "question": "e",
          "solution": "and",
          "additionText": "e"
      },
      {
          "id": "76",
          "question": "vida",
          "solution": "life",
          "additionText": "life"
      },
      {
          "id": "77",
          "question": "otro",
          "solution": "other",
          "additionText": "another"
      },
      {
          "id": "78",
          "question": "después",
          "solution": "after",
          "additionText": "then"
      },
      {
          "id": "79",
          "question": "te",
          "solution": "tea",
          "additionText": "you"
      },
      {
          "id": "80",
          "question": "otros",
          "solution": "others",
          "additionText": "others"
      },
      {
          "id": "81",
          "question": "aunque",
          "solution": "even though",
          "additionText": "even if"
      },
      {
          "id": "82",
          "question": "esa",
          "solution": "that",
          "additionText": "that"
      },
      {
          "id": "83",
          "question": "eso",
          "solution": "that",
          "additionText": "that"
      },
      {
          "id": "84",
          "question": "hace",
          "solution": "make",
          "additionText": "makes"
      },
      {
          "id": "85",
          "question": "otra",
          "solution": "other",
          "additionText": "another"
      },
      {
          "id": "86",
          "question": "gobierno",
          "solution": "government",
          "additionText": "government"
      },
      {
          "id": "87",
          "question": "tan",
          "solution": "so",
          "additionText": "so"
      },
      {
          "id": "88",
          "question": "durante",
          "solution": "during",
          "additionText": "during"
      },
      {
          "id": "89",
          "question": "siempre",
          "solution": "forever",
          "additionText": "always"
      },
      {
          "id": "90",
          "question": "día",
          "solution": "day",
          "additionText": "day"
      },
      {
          "id": "91",
          "question": "tanto",
          "solution": "so much",
          "additionText": "so much"
      },
      {
          "id": "92",
          "question": "ella",
          "solution": "she",
          "additionText": "she"
      },
      {
          "id": "93",
          "question": "tres",
          "solution": "three",
          "additionText": "three"
      },
      {
          "id": "94",
          "question": "sí",
          "solution": "Yes",
          "additionText": "yes"
      },
      {
          "id": "95",
          "question": "dijo",
          "solution": "He said",
          "additionText": "said"
      },
      {
          "id": "96",
          "question": "sido",
          "solution": "been",
          "additionText": "been"
      },
      {
          "id": "97",
          "question": "gran",
          "solution": "big",
          "additionText": "great"
      },
      {
          "id": "98",
          "question": "país",
          "solution": "country",
          "additionText": "country"
      },
      {
          "id": "99",
          "question": "según",
          "solution": "according to",
          "additionText": "according to"
      },
      {
          "id": "100",
          "question": "menos",
          "solution": "less",
          "additionText": "less"
      },
      {
          "id": "101",
          "question": "mundo",
          "solution": "world",
          "additionText": "world"
      },
      {
          "id": "102",
          "question": "año",
          "solution": "year",
          "additionText": "year"
      },
      {
          "id": "103",
          "question": "antes",
          "solution": "before",
          "additionText": "before"
      },
      {
          "id": "104",
          "question": "estado",
          "solution": "condition",
          "additionText": "state"
      },
      {
          "id": "105",
          "question": "contra",
          "solution": "against",
          "additionText": "against"
      },
      {
          "id": "106",
          "question": "sino",
          "solution": "otherwise",
          "additionText": "but"
      },
      {
          "id": "107",
          "question": "forma",
          "solution": "form",
          "additionText": "form"
      },
      {
          "id": "108",
          "question": "caso",
          "solution": "case",
          "additionText": "case"
      },
      {
          "id": "109",
          "question": "nada",
          "solution": "nothing",
          "additionText": "nothing"
      },
      {
          "id": "110",
          "question": "hacer",
          "solution": "do",
          "additionText": "do"
      },
      {
          "id": "111",
          "question": "general",
          "solution": "general",
          "additionText": "general"
      },
      {
          "id": "112",
          "question": "estaba",
          "solution": "I was",
          "additionText": "was"
      },
      {
          "id": "113",
          "question": "poco",
          "solution": "little bit",
          "additionText": "little"
      },
      {
          "id": "114",
          "question": "estos",
          "solution": "these",
          "additionText": "these"
      },
      {
          "id": "115",
          "question": "presidente",
          "solution": "President",
          "additionText": "president"
      },
      {
          "id": "116",
          "question": "mayor",
          "solution": "higher",
          "additionText": "major"
      },
      {
          "id": "117",
          "question": "ante",
          "solution": "in view of",
          "additionText": "to"
      },
      {
          "id": "118",
          "question": "unos",
          "solution": "some",
          "additionText": "some"
      },
      {
          "id": "119",
          "question": "les",
          "solution": "them",
          "additionText": "them"
      },
      {
          "id": "120",
          "question": "algo",
          "solution": "something",
          "additionText": "somewhat"
      },
      {
          "id": "121",
          "question": "hacia",
          "solution": "toward",
          "additionText": "to"
      },
      {
          "id": "122",
          "question": "casa",
          "solution": "home",
          "additionText": "home"
      },
      {
          "id": "123",
          "question": "ellos",
          "solution": "they",
          "additionText": "they"
      },
      {
          "id": "124",
          "question": "ayer",
          "solution": "Yesterday",
          "additionText": "yesterday"
      },
      {
          "id": "125",
          "question": "hecho",
          "solution": "done",
          "additionText": "fact"
      },
      {
          "id": "126",
          "question": "primera",
          "solution": "first",
          "additionText": "first"
      },
      {
          "id": "127",
          "question": "mucho",
          "solution": "a lot",
          "additionText": "much"
      },
      {
          "id": "128",
          "question": "mientras",
          "solution": "While",
          "additionText": "while"
      },
      {
          "id": "129",
          "question": "además",
          "solution": "what's more",
          "additionText": "moreover"
      },
      {
          "id": "130",
          "question": "quien",
          "solution": "who",
          "additionText": "who"
      },
      {
          "id": "131",
          "question": "momento",
          "solution": "moment",
          "additionText": "time"
      },
      {
          "id": "132",
          "question": "millones",
          "solution": "millions",
          "additionText": "millions"
      },
      {
          "id": "133",
          "question": "esto",
          "solution": "this",
          "additionText": "this"
      },
      {
          "id": "134",
          "question": "españa",
          "solution": "Spain",
          "additionText": "spain"
      },
      {
          "id": "135",
          "question": "hombre",
          "solution": "man",
          "additionText": "man"
      },
      {
          "id": "136",
          "question": "están",
          "solution": "is it so",
          "additionText": "are"
      },
      {
          "id": "137",
          "question": "pues",
          "solution": "well",
          "additionText": "because"
      },
      {
          "id": "138",
          "question": "hoy",
          "solution": "today",
          "additionText": "today"
      },
      {
          "id": "139",
          "question": "lugar",
          "solution": "place",
          "additionText": "place"
      },
      {
          "id": "140",
          "question": "madrid",
          "solution": "Madrid",
          "additionText": "madrid"
      },
      {
          "id": "141",
          "question": "nacional",
          "solution": "national",
          "additionText": "national"
      },
      {
          "id": "142",
          "question": "trabajo",
          "solution": "job",
          "additionText": "job"
      },
      {
          "id": "143",
          "question": "otras",
          "solution": "other",
          "additionText": "other"
      },
      {
          "id": "144",
          "question": "mejor",
          "solution": "better",
          "additionText": "best"
      },
      {
          "id": "145",
          "question": "nuevo",
          "solution": "new",
          "additionText": "new"
      },
      {
          "id": "146",
          "question": "decir",
          "solution": "tell",
          "additionText": "say"
      },
      {
          "id": "147",
          "question": "algunos",
          "solution": "Some",
          "additionText": "some"
      },
      {
          "id": "148",
          "question": "entonces",
          "solution": "then",
          "additionText": "then"
      },
      {
          "id": "149",
          "question": "todas",
          "solution": "all",
          "additionText": "all"
      },
      {
          "id": "150",
          "question": "días",
          "solution": "days",
          "additionText": "days"
      },
      {
          "id": "151",
          "question": "debe",
          "solution": "has to",
          "additionText": "should"
      },
      {
          "id": "152",
          "question": "política",
          "solution": "politics",
          "additionText": "policy"
      },
      {
          "id": "153",
          "question": "cómo",
          "solution": "excuse me",
          "additionText": "how"
      },
      {
          "id": "154",
          "question": "casi",
          "solution": "almost",
          "additionText": "almost"
      },
      {
          "id": "155",
          "question": "toda",
          "solution": "all",
          "additionText": "all"
      },
      {
          "id": "156",
          "question": "tal",
          "solution": "such",
          "additionText": "such"
      },
      {
          "id": "157",
          "question": "luego",
          "solution": "later",
          "additionText": "then"
      },
      {
          "id": "158",
          "question": "pasado",
          "solution": "last",
          "additionText": "past"
      },
      {
          "id": "159",
          "question": "primer",
          "solution": "first",
          "additionText": "first"
      },
      {
          "id": "160",
          "question": "medio",
          "solution": "half",
          "additionText": "half"
      },
      {
          "id": "161",
          "question": "va",
          "solution": "he",
          "additionText": "goes"
      },
      {
          "id": "162",
          "question": "estas",
          "solution": "are",
          "additionText": "these"
      },
      {
          "id": "163",
          "question": "sea",
          "solution": "be",
          "additionText": "be"
      },
      {
          "id": "164",
          "question": "tenía",
          "solution": "I had",
          "additionText": "had"
      },
      {
          "id": "165",
          "question": "nunca",
          "solution": "never",
          "additionText": "never"
      },
      {
          "id": "166",
          "question": "poder",
          "solution": "can",
          "additionText": "power"
      },
      {
          "id": "167",
          "question": "aquí",
          "solution": "here",
          "additionText": "here"
      },
      {
          "id": "168",
          "question": "ver",
          "solution": "watch",
          "additionText": "see"
      },
      {
          "id": "169",
          "question": "veces",
          "solution": "times",
          "additionText": "times"
      },
      {
          "id": "170",
          "question": "embargo",
          "solution": "embargo",
          "additionText": "embargo"
      },
      {
          "id": "171",
          "question": "partido",
          "solution": "match",
          "additionText": "party"
      },
      {
          "id": "172",
          "question": "personas",
          "solution": "persons",
          "additionText": "people"
      },
      {
          "id": "173",
          "question": "grupo",
          "solution": "group",
          "additionText": "group"
      },
      {
          "id": "174",
          "question": "cuenta",
          "solution": "bill",
          "additionText": "account"
      },
      {
          "id": "175",
          "question": "pueden",
          "solution": "they can",
          "additionText": "can"
      },
      {
          "id": "176",
          "question": "tienen",
          "solution": "have",
          "additionText": "have"
      },
      {
          "id": "177",
          "question": "misma",
          "solution": "same",
          "additionText": "same"
      },
      {
          "id": "178",
          "question": "nueva",
          "solution": "new",
          "additionText": "new"
      },
      {
          "id": "179",
          "question": "cual",
          "solution": "which",
          "additionText": "which"
      },
      {
          "id": "180",
          "question": "fueron",
          "solution": "They were",
          "additionText": "were"
      },
      {
          "id": "181",
          "question": "mujer",
          "solution": "woman",
          "additionText": "woman"
      },
      {
          "id": "182",
          "question": "frente",
          "solution": "forehead",
          "additionText": "front"
      },
      {
          "id": "183",
          "question": "josé",
          "solution": "Joseph",
          "additionText": "joseph"
      },
      {
          "id": "184",
          "question": "tras",
          "solution": "after",
          "additionText": "behind"
      },
      {
          "id": "185",
          "question": "cosas",
          "solution": "things",
          "additionText": "things"
      },
      {
          "id": "186",
          "question": "fin",
          "solution": "finish",
          "additionText": "end"
      },
      {
          "id": "187",
          "question": "ciudad",
          "solution": "city",
          "additionText": "city"
      },
      {
          "id": "188",
          "question": "he",
          "solution": "I",
          "additionText": "he"
      },
      {
          "id": "189",
          "question": "social",
          "solution": "Social",
          "additionText": "social"
      },
      {
          "id": "190",
          "question": "manera",
          "solution": "way",
          "additionText": "way"
      },
      {
          "id": "191",
          "question": "tener",
          "solution": "have",
          "additionText": "have"
      },
      {
          "id": "192",
          "question": "sistema",
          "solution": "system",
          "additionText": "system"
      },
      {
          "id": "193",
          "question": "será",
          "solution": "be",
          "additionText": "will be"
      },
      {
          "id": "194",
          "question": "historia",
          "solution": "history",
          "additionText": "history"
      },
      {
          "id": "195",
          "question": "muchos",
          "solution": "Many",
          "additionText": "many"
      },
      {
          "id": "196",
          "question": "juan",
          "solution": "John",
          "additionText": "juan"
      },
      {
          "id": "197",
          "question": "tipo",
          "solution": "kind",
          "additionText": "type"
      },
      {
          "id": "198",
          "question": "cuatro",
          "solution": "four",
          "additionText": "four"
      },
      {
          "id": "199",
          "question": "dentro",
          "solution": "inside",
          "additionText": "inside"
      },
      {
          "id": "200",
          "question": "nuestro",
          "solution": "our",
          "additionText": "our"
      },
      {
          "id": "201",
          "question": "punto",
          "solution": "point",
          "additionText": "dot"
      },
      {
          "id": "202",
          "question": "dice",
          "solution": "He says",
          "additionText": "it says"
      },
      {
          "id": "203",
          "question": "ello",
          "solution": "it",
          "additionText": "it"
      },
      {
          "id": "204",
          "question": "cualquier",
          "solution": "any",
          "additionText": "any"
      },
      {
          "id": "205",
          "question": "noche",
          "solution": "night",
          "additionText": "night"
      },
      {
          "id": "206",
          "question": "aún",
          "solution": "still",
          "additionText": "even"
      },
      {
          "id": "207",
          "question": "agua",
          "solution": "Water",
          "additionText": "water"
      },
      {
          "id": "208",
          "question": "parece",
          "solution": "It seems",
          "additionText": "it seems"
      },
      {
          "id": "209",
          "question": "haber",
          "solution": "to have",
          "additionText": "to have"
      },
      {
          "id": "210",
          "question": "situación",
          "solution": "situation",
          "additionText": "situation"
      },
      {
          "id": "211",
          "question": "fuera",
          "solution": "outside",
          "additionText": "outside"
      },
      {
          "id": "212",
          "question": "bajo",
          "solution": "under",
          "additionText": "under"
      },
      {
          "id": "213",
          "question": "grandes",
          "solution": "big",
          "additionText": "great"
      },
      {
          "id": "214",
          "question": "nuestra",
          "solution": "our",
          "additionText": "our"
      },
      {
          "id": "215",
          "question": "ejemplo",
          "solution": "example",
          "additionText": "example"
      },
      {
          "id": "216",
          "question": "acuerdo",
          "solution": "agreement",
          "additionText": "agreement"
      },
      {
          "id": "217",
          "question": "habían",
          "solution": "they had",
          "additionText": "you had"
      },
      {
          "id": "218",
          "question": "usted",
          "solution": "you",
          "additionText": "you"
      },
      {
          "id": "219",
          "question": "estados",
          "solution": "state",
          "additionText": "states"
      },
      {
          "id": "220",
          "question": "hizo",
          "solution": "made",
          "additionText": "made"
      },
      {
          "id": "221",
          "question": "nadie",
          "solution": "nobody",
          "additionText": "no one"
      },
      {
          "id": "222",
          "question": "países",
          "solution": "countries",
          "additionText": "countries"
      },
      {
          "id": "223",
          "question": "horas",
          "solution": "hours",
          "additionText": "hours"
      },
      {
          "id": "224",
          "question": "posible",
          "solution": "possible",
          "additionText": "possible"
      },
      {
          "id": "225",
          "question": "tarde",
          "solution": "late",
          "additionText": "afternoon"
      },
      {
          "id": "226",
          "question": "ley",
          "solution": "law",
          "additionText": "law"
      },
      {
          "id": "227",
          "question": "importante",
          "solution": "important",
          "additionText": "important"
      },
      {
          "id": "228",
          "question": "guerra",
          "solution": "war",
          "additionText": "war"
      },
      {
          "id": "229",
          "question": "desarrollo",
          "solution": "developing",
          "additionText": "development"
      },
      {
          "id": "230",
          "question": "proceso",
          "solution": "process",
          "additionText": "process"
      },
      {
          "id": "231",
          "question": "realidad",
          "solution": "reality",
          "additionText": "reality"
      },
      {
          "id": "232",
          "question": "sentido",
          "solution": "sense",
          "additionText": "meaning"
      },
      {
          "id": "233",
          "question": "lado",
          "solution": "side",
          "additionText": "side"
      },
      {
          "id": "234",
          "question": "mí",
          "solution": "my",
          "additionText": "me"
      },
      {
          "id": "235",
          "question": "tu",
          "solution": "you",
          "additionText": "your"
      },
      {
          "id": "236",
          "question": "cambio",
          "solution": "change",
          "additionText": "change"
      },
      {
          "id": "237",
          "question": "allí",
          "solution": "there",
          "additionText": "there"
      },
      {
          "id": "238",
          "question": "mano",
          "solution": "hand",
          "additionText": "hand"
      },
      {
          "id": "239",
          "question": "eran",
          "solution": "were",
          "additionText": "were"
      },
      {
          "id": "240",
          "question": "estar",
          "solution": "to be",
          "additionText": "be"
      },
      {
          "id": "241",
          "question": "san",
          "solution": "saint",
          "additionText": "saint"
      },
      {
          "id": "242",
          "question": "número",
          "solution": "number",
          "additionText": "number"
      },
      {
          "id": "243",
          "question": "sociedad",
          "solution": "society",
          "additionText": "company"
      },
      {
          "id": "244",
          "question": "unas",
          "solution": "nails",
          "additionText": "about"
      },
      {
          "id": "245",
          "question": "centro",
          "solution": "center",
          "additionText": "center"
      },
      {
          "id": "246",
          "question": "padre",
          "solution": "dad",
          "additionText": "father"
      },
      {
          "id": "247",
          "question": "gente",
          "solution": "people",
          "additionText": "people"
      },
      {
          "id": "248",
          "question": "final",
          "solution": "final",
          "additionText": "end"
      },
      {
          "id": "249",
          "question": "relación",
          "solution": "relationship",
          "additionText": "relationship"
      },
      {
          "id": "250",
          "question": "cuerpo",
          "solution": "body",
          "additionText": "body"
      },
      {
          "id": "251",
          "question": "obra",
          "solution": "construction site",
          "additionText": "work"
      },
      {
          "id": "252",
          "question": "incluso",
          "solution": "even",
          "additionText": "including"
      },
      {
          "id": "253",
          "question": "través",
          "solution": "through",
          "additionText": "through"
      },
      {
          "id": "254",
          "question": "último",
          "solution": "latest",
          "additionText": "last"
      },
      {
          "id": "255",
          "question": "madre",
          "solution": "mother",
          "additionText": "mother"
      },
      {
          "id": "256",
          "question": "mis",
          "solution": "my",
          "additionText": "my"
      },
      {
          "id": "257",
          "question": "modo",
          "solution": "mode",
          "additionText": "mode"
      },
      {
          "id": "258",
          "question": "problemas",
          "solution": "problems",
          "additionText": "problems"
      },
      {
          "id": "259",
          "question": "cinco",
          "solution": "five",
          "additionText": "five"
      },
      {
          "id": "260",
          "question": "carlos",
          "solution": "Carlos",
          "additionText": "carlos"
      },
      {
          "id": "261",
          "question": "hombres",
          "solution": "mens",
          "additionText": "men"
      },
      {
          "id": "262",
          "question": "información",
          "solution": "information",
          "additionText": "information"
      },
      {
          "id": "263",
          "question": "ojos",
          "solution": "eyes",
          "additionText": "eyes"
      },
      {
          "id": "264",
          "question": "muerte",
          "solution": "death",
          "additionText": "death"
      },
      {
          "id": "265",
          "question": "nombre",
          "solution": "Name",
          "additionText": "name"
      },
      {
          "id": "266",
          "question": "algunas",
          "solution": "some",
          "additionText": "some"
      },
      {
          "id": "267",
          "question": "público",
          "solution": "public",
          "additionText": "public"
      },
      {
          "id": "268",
          "question": "mujeres",
          "solution": "women",
          "additionText": "women"
      },
      {
          "id": "269",
          "question": "siglo",
          "solution": "century",
          "additionText": "century"
      },
      {
          "id": "270",
          "question": "todavía",
          "solution": "yet",
          "additionText": "still"
      },
      {
          "id": "271",
          "question": "meses",
          "solution": "months",
          "additionText": "months"
      },
      {
          "id": "272",
          "question": "mañana",
          "solution": "morning",
          "additionText": "tomorrow"
      },
      {
          "id": "273",
          "question": "esos",
          "solution": "those",
          "additionText": "those"
      },
      {
          "id": "274",
          "question": "nosotros",
          "solution": "We",
          "additionText": "we"
      },
      {
          "id": "275",
          "question": "hora",
          "solution": "hour",
          "additionText": "time"
      },
      {
          "id": "276",
          "question": "muchas",
          "solution": "many",
          "additionText": "many"
      },
      {
          "id": "277",
          "question": "pueblo",
          "solution": "town",
          "additionText": "people"
      },
      {
          "id": "278",
          "question": "alguna",
          "solution": "some",
          "additionText": "some"
      },
      {
          "id": "279",
          "question": "dar",
          "solution": "give",
          "additionText": "give"
      },
      {
          "id": "280",
          "question": "problema",
          "solution": "issue",
          "additionText": "problem"
      },
      {
          "id": "281",
          "question": "don",
          "solution": "Don",
          "additionText": "don"
      },
      {
          "id": "282",
          "question": "da",
          "solution": "gives",
          "additionText": "da"
      },
      {
          "id": "283",
          "question": "tú",
          "solution": "your",
          "additionText": "you"
      },
      {
          "id": "284",
          "question": "derecho",
          "solution": "right",
          "additionText": "right"
      },
      {
          "id": "285",
          "question": "verdad",
          "solution": "truth",
          "additionText": "truth"
      },
      {
          "id": "286",
          "question": "maría",
          "solution": "Mary",
          "additionText": "mary"
      },
      {
          "id": "287",
          "question": "unidos",
          "solution": "joined",
          "additionText": "united"
      },
      {
          "id": "288",
          "question": "podría",
          "solution": "might",
          "additionText": "could"
      },
      {
          "id": "289",
          "question": "sería",
          "solution": "would",
          "additionText": "would be"
      },
      {
          "id": "290",
          "question": "junto",
          "solution": "together",
          "additionText": "together"
      },
      {
          "id": "291",
          "question": "cabeza",
          "solution": "head",
          "additionText": "head"
      },
      {
          "id": "292",
          "question": "aquel",
          "solution": "that",
          "additionText": "that"
      },
      {
          "id": "293",
          "question": "luis",
          "solution": "Lewis",
          "additionText": "luis"
      },
      {
          "id": "294",
          "question": "cuanto",
          "solution": "how much",
          "additionText": "how much"
      },
      {
          "id": "295",
          "question": "tierra",
          "solution": "land",
          "additionText": "earth"
      },
      {
          "id": "296",
          "question": "equipo",
          "solution": "team",
          "additionText": "team"
      },
      {
          "id": "297",
          "question": "segundo",
          "solution": "second",
          "additionText": "second"
      },
      {
          "id": "298",
          "question": "director",
          "solution": "director",
          "additionText": "director"
      },
      {
          "id": "299",
          "question": "dicho",
          "solution": "saying",
          "additionText": "said"
      },
      {
          "id": "300",
          "question": "cierto",
          "solution": "certain",
          "additionText": "TRUE"
      },
      {
          "id": "301",
          "question": "casos",
          "solution": "cases",
          "additionText": "cases"
      },
      {
          "id": "302",
          "question": "manos",
          "solution": "hands",
          "additionText": "hands"
      },
      {
          "id": "303",
          "question": "nivel",
          "solution": "level",
          "additionText": "level"
      },
      {
          "id": "304",
          "question": "podía",
          "solution": "I could",
          "additionText": "could"
      },
      {
          "id": "305",
          "question": "familia",
          "solution": "family",
          "additionText": "family"
      },
      {
          "id": "306",
          "question": "largo",
          "solution": "length",
          "additionText": "long"
      },
      {
          "id": "307",
          "question": "partir",
          "solution": "from",
          "additionText": "split"
      },
      {
          "id": "308",
          "question": "falta",
          "solution": "lack",
          "additionText": "missing"
      },
      {
          "id": "309",
          "question": "llegar",
          "solution": "reach",
          "additionText": "arrive"
      },
      {
          "id": "310",
          "question": "propio",
          "solution": "own",
          "additionText": "own"
      },
      {
          "id": "311",
          "question": "ministro",
          "solution": "Minister",
          "additionText": "minister"
      },
      {
          "id": "312",
          "question": "cosa",
          "solution": "thing",
          "additionText": "thing"
      },
      {
          "id": "313",
          "question": "primero",
          "solution": "first",
          "additionText": "first"
      },
      {
          "id": "314",
          "question": "seguridad",
          "solution": "security",
          "additionText": "security"
      },
      {
          "id": "315",
          "question": "hemos",
          "solution": "we have",
          "additionText": "we have"
      },
      {
          "id": "316",
          "question": "mal",
          "solution": "wrong",
          "additionText": "wrong"
      },
      {
          "id": "317",
          "question": "trata",
          "solution": "about",
          "additionText": "try"
      },
      {
          "id": "318",
          "question": "algún",
          "solution": "some",
          "additionText": "some"
      },
      {
          "id": "319",
          "question": "tuvo",
          "solution": "had",
          "additionText": "had"
      },
      {
          "id": "320",
          "question": "respecto",
          "solution": "respect",
          "additionText": "about"
      },
      {
          "id": "321",
          "question": "semana",
          "solution": "week",
          "additionText": "week"
      },
      {
          "id": "322",
          "question": "varios",
          "solution": "several",
          "additionText": "several"
      },
      {
          "id": "323",
          "question": "real",
          "solution": "real",
          "additionText": "real"
      },
      {
          "id": "324",
          "question": "sé",
          "solution": "he",
          "additionText": "I know"
      },
      {
          "id": "325",
          "question": "voz",
          "solution": "voice",
          "additionText": "voice"
      },
      {
          "id": "326",
          "question": "paso",
          "solution": "He passed",
          "additionText": "step"
      },
      {
          "id": "327",
          "question": "señor",
          "solution": "Sir",
          "additionText": "Mr."
      },
      {
          "id": "328",
          "question": "mil",
          "solution": "one thousand",
          "additionText": "one thousand"
      },
      {
          "id": "329",
          "question": "quienes",
          "solution": "Who",
          "additionText": "who"
      },
      {
          "id": "330",
          "question": "proyecto",
          "solution": "draft",
          "additionText": "project"
      },
      {
          "id": "331",
          "question": "mercado",
          "solution": "market",
          "additionText": "market"
      },
      {
          "id": "332",
          "question": "mayoría",
          "solution": "most",
          "additionText": "majority"
      },
      {
          "id": "333",
          "question": "luz",
          "solution": "light",
          "additionText": "light"
      },
      {
          "id": "334",
          "question": "claro",
          "solution": "Sure",
          "additionText": "clear"
      },
      {
          "id": "335",
          "question": "iba",
          "solution": "I was going",
          "additionText": "iba"
      },
      {
          "id": "336",
          "question": "éste",
          "solution": "East",
          "additionText": "this one"
      },
      {
          "id": "337",
          "question": "pesetas",
          "solution": "pesetas",
          "additionText": "pesetas"
      },
      {
          "id": "338",
          "question": "orden",
          "solution": "order",
          "additionText": "order"
      },
      {
          "id": "339",
          "question": "español",
          "solution": "Spanish",
          "additionText": "Spanish"
      },
      {
          "id": "340",
          "question": "buena",
          "solution": "good",
          "additionText": "good"
      },
      {
          "id": "341",
          "question": "quiere",
          "solution": "wants",
          "additionText": "wants"
      },
      {
          "id": "342",
          "question": "aquella",
          "solution": "that",
          "additionText": "that"
      },
      {
          "id": "343",
          "question": "programa",
          "solution": "Program",
          "additionText": "program"
      },
      {
          "id": "344",
          "question": "palabras",
          "solution": "words",
          "additionText": "words"
      },
      {
          "id": "345",
          "question": "internacional",
          "solution": "international",
          "additionText": "international"
      },
      {
          "id": "346",
          "question": "van",
          "solution": "go",
          "additionText": "go"
      },
      {
          "id": "347",
          "question": "esas",
          "solution": "those",
          "additionText": "those"
      },
      {
          "id": "348",
          "question": "segunda",
          "solution": "second",
          "additionText": "second"
      },
      {
          "id": "349",
          "question": "empresa",
          "solution": "business",
          "additionText": "company"
      },
      {
          "id": "350",
          "question": "puesto",
          "solution": "Market Stall"
      },
      {
          "id": "351",
          "question": "ahí",
          "solution": "there",
          "additionText": "there"
      },
      {
          "id": "352",
          "question": "propia",
          "solution": "own",
          "additionText": "own"
      },
      {
          "id": "353",
          "question": "m",
          "solution": "m",
          "additionText": "m"
      },
      {
          "id": "354",
          "question": "libro",
          "solution": "book",
          "additionText": "book"
      },
      {
          "id": "355",
          "question": "igual",
          "solution": "same",
          "additionText": "same"
      },
      {
          "id": "356",
          "question": "político",
          "solution": "politician",
          "additionText": "politician"
      },
      {
          "id": "357",
          "question": "persona",
          "solution": "person",
          "additionText": "person"
      },
      {
          "id": "358",
          "question": "últimos",
          "solution": "latest",
          "additionText": "last"
      },
      {
          "id": "359",
          "question": "ellas",
          "solution": "they",
          "additionText": "they"
      },
      {
          "id": "360",
          "question": "total",
          "solution": "total",
          "additionText": "total"
      },
      {
          "id": "361",
          "question": "creo",
          "solution": "I think",
          "additionText": "I think"
      },
      {
          "id": "362",
          "question": "tengo",
          "solution": "have",
          "additionText": "I have"
      },
      {
          "id": "363",
          "question": "dios",
          "solution": "God",
          "additionText": "god"
      },
      {
          "id": "364",
          "question": "c",
          "solution": "c",
          "additionText": "c"
      },
      {
          "id": "365",
          "question": "española",
          "solution": "Spanish",
          "additionText": "spanish"
      },
      {
          "id": "366",
          "question": "condiciones",
          "solution": "terms",
          "additionText": "conditions"
      },
      {
          "id": "367",
          "question": "méxico",
          "solution": "Mexico",
          "additionText": "mexico"
      },
      {
          "id": "368",
          "question": "fuerza",
          "solution": "force",
          "additionText": "force"
      },
      {
          "id": "369",
          "question": "solo",
          "solution": "only",
          "additionText": "only"
      },
      {
          "id": "370",
          "question": "único",
          "solution": "unique",
          "additionText": "only"
      },
      {
          "id": "371",
          "question": "acción",
          "solution": "action",
          "additionText": "action"
      },
      {
          "id": "372",
          "question": "amor",
          "solution": "love",
          "additionText": "love"
      },
      {
          "id": "373",
          "question": "policía",
          "solution": "policeman",
          "additionText": "police"
      },
      {
          "id": "374",
          "question": "puerta",
          "solution": "door",
          "additionText": "door"
      },
      {
          "id": "375",
          "question": "pesar",
          "solution": "to weigh",
          "additionText": "regret"
      },
      {
          "id": "376",
          "question": "zona",
          "solution": "zone",
          "additionText": "zone"
      },
      {
          "id": "377",
          "question": "sabe",
          "solution": "knows",
          "additionText": "you know"
      },
      {
          "id": "378",
          "question": "calle",
          "solution": "Street",
          "additionText": "street"
      },
      {
          "id": "379",
          "question": "interior",
          "solution": "inside",
          "additionText": "inside"
      },
      {
          "id": "380",
          "question": "tampoco",
          "solution": "either",
          "additionText": "also"
      },
      {
          "id": "381",
          "question": "música",
          "solution": "music",
          "additionText": "music"
      },
      {
          "id": "382",
          "question": "ningún",
          "solution": "any",
          "additionText": "no"
      },
      {
          "id": "383",
          "question": "vista",
          "solution": "sight",
          "additionText": "view"
      },
      {
          "id": "384",
          "question": "campo",
          "solution": "countryside",
          "additionText": "field"
      },
      {
          "id": "385",
          "question": "buen",
          "solution": "good",
          "additionText": "good"
      },
      {
          "id": "386",
          "question": "hubiera",
          "solution": "had",
          "additionText": "would have"
      },
      {
          "id": "387",
          "question": "saber",
          "solution": "to know",
          "additionText": "know"
      },
      {
          "id": "388",
          "question": "obras",
          "solution": "plays",
          "additionText": "works"
      },
      {
          "id": "389",
          "question": "razón",
          "solution": "reason",
          "additionText": "reason"
      },
      {
          "id": "390",
          "question": "ex",
          "solution": "former",
          "additionText": "ex"
      },
      {
          "id": "391",
          "question": "niños",
          "solution": "children",
          "additionText": "children"
      },
      {
          "id": "392",
          "question": "presencia",
          "solution": "presence",
          "additionText": "presence"
      },
      {
          "id": "393",
          "question": "tema",
          "solution": "theme",
          "additionText": "theme"
      },
      {
          "id": "394",
          "question": "dinero",
          "solution": "money",
          "additionText": "money"
      },
      {
          "id": "395",
          "question": "comisión",
          "solution": "commission",
          "additionText": "commission"
      },
      {
          "id": "396",
          "question": "antonio",
          "solution": "Anthony",
          "additionText": "antonio"
      },
      {
          "id": "397",
          "question": "servicio",
          "solution": "service",
          "additionText": "service"
      },
      {
          "id": "398",
          "question": "hijo",
          "solution": "son",
          "additionText": "son"
      },
      {
          "id": "399",
          "question": "última",
          "solution": "last",
          "additionText": "last"
      },
      {
          "id": "400",
          "question": "ciento",
          "solution": "hundred",
          "additionText": "one hundred"
      },
      {
          "id": "401",
          "question": "estoy",
          "solution": "I'm",
          "additionText": "I am"
      },
      {
          "id": "402",
          "question": "hablar",
          "solution": "speak",
          "additionText": "speak"
      },
      {
          "id": "403",
          "question": "dio",
          "solution": "it gave",
          "additionText": "gave"
      },
      {
          "id": "404",
          "question": "minutos",
          "solution": "minutes",
          "additionText": "minutes"
      },
      {
          "id": "405",
          "question": "producción",
          "solution": "production",
          "additionText": "production"
      },
      {
          "id": "406",
          "question": "camino",
          "solution": "road",
          "additionText": "way"
      },
      {
          "id": "407",
          "question": "seis",
          "solution": "six",
          "additionText": "six"
      },
      {
          "id": "408",
          "question": "quién",
          "solution": "who",
          "additionText": "who"
      },
      {
          "id": "409",
          "question": "fondo",
          "solution": "background",
          "additionText": "background"
      },
      {
          "id": "410",
          "question": "dirección",
          "solution": "address",
          "additionText": "address"
      },
      {
          "id": "411",
          "question": "papel",
          "solution": "paper",
          "additionText": "role"
      },
      {
          "id": "412",
          "question": "demás",
          "solution": "the rest",
          "additionText": "other"
      },
      {
          "id": "413",
          "question": "barcelona",
          "solution": "Barcelona",
          "additionText": "barcelona"
      },
      {
          "id": "414",
          "question": "idea",
          "solution": "idea",
          "additionText": "idea"
      },
      {
          "id": "415",
          "question": "especial",
          "solution": "special",
          "additionText": "special"
      },
      {
          "id": "416",
          "question": "diferentes",
          "solution": "different",
          "additionText": "different"
      },
      {
          "id": "417",
          "question": "dado",
          "solution": "dice",
          "additionText": "die"
      },
      {
          "id": "418",
          "question": "base",
          "solution": "base",
          "additionText": "base"
      },
      {
          "id": "419",
          "question": "capital",
          "solution": "capital",
          "additionText": "capital"
      },
      {
          "id": "420",
          "question": "ambos",
          "solution": "both of them",
          "additionText": "both"
      },
      {
          "id": "421",
          "question": "europa",
          "solution": "Europe",
          "additionText": "europe"
      },
      {
          "id": "422",
          "question": "libertad",
          "solution": "freedom",
          "additionText": "freedom"
      },
      {
          "id": "423",
          "question": "relaciones",
          "solution": "relations",
          "additionText": "relations"
      },
      {
          "id": "424",
          "question": "espacio",
          "solution": "space",
          "additionText": "space"
      },
      {
          "id": "425",
          "question": "medios",
          "solution": "media",
          "additionText": "media"
      },
      {
          "id": "426",
          "question": "ir",
          "solution": "to go",
          "additionText": "go"
      },
      {
          "id": "427",
          "question": "actual",
          "solution": "current",
          "additionText": "current"
      },
      {
          "id": "428",
          "question": "población",
          "solution": "population",
          "additionText": "population"
      },
      {
          "id": "429",
          "question": "empresas",
          "solution": "Business",
          "additionText": "companies"
      },
      {
          "id": "430",
          "question": "estudio",
          "solution": "study",
          "additionText": "study"
      },
      {
          "id": "431",
          "question": "salud",
          "solution": "Health",
          "additionText": "health"
      },
      {
          "id": "432",
          "question": "servicios",
          "solution": "services",
          "additionText": "services"
      },
      {
          "id": "433",
          "question": "haya",
          "solution": "is",
          "additionText": "beech"
      },
      {
          "id": "434",
          "question": "principio",
          "solution": "beginning",
          "additionText": "principle"
      },
      {
          "id": "435",
          "question": "siendo",
          "solution": "being",
          "additionText": "being"
      },
      {
          "id": "436",
          "question": "cultura",
          "solution": "culture",
          "additionText": "culture"
      },
      {
          "id": "437",
          "question": "anterior",
          "solution": "previous",
          "additionText": "previous"
      },
      {
          "id": "438",
          "question": "alto",
          "solution": "high",
          "additionText": "high"
      },
      {
          "id": "439",
          "question": "media",
          "solution": "half",
          "additionText": "average"
      },
      {
          "id": "440",
          "question": "mediante",
          "solution": "through",
          "additionText": "via"
      },
      {
          "id": "441",
          "question": "primeros",
          "solution": "first",
          "additionText": "early"
      },
      {
          "id": "442",
          "question": "arte",
          "solution": "art",
          "additionText": "art"
      },
      {
          "id": "443",
          "question": "paz",
          "solution": "peace",
          "additionText": "peace"
      },
      {
          "id": "444",
          "question": "sector",
          "solution": "sector",
          "additionText": "sector"
      },
      {
          "id": "445",
          "question": "imagen",
          "solution": "image",
          "additionText": "image"
      },
      {
          "id": "446",
          "question": "medida",
          "solution": "measure",
          "additionText": "measure"
      },
      {
          "id": "447",
          "question": "deben",
          "solution": "should",
          "additionText": "you must"
      },
      {
          "id": "448",
          "question": "datos",
          "solution": "data",
          "additionText": "data"
      },
      {
          "id": "449",
          "question": "consejo",
          "solution": "tip",
          "additionText": "board"
      },
      {
          "id": "450",
          "question": "personal",
          "solution": "personal",
          "additionText": "staff"
      },
      {
          "id": "451",
          "question": "interés",
          "solution": "interest",
          "additionText": "interest"
      },
      {
          "id": "452",
          "question": "julio",
          "solution": "July",
          "additionText": "july"
      },
      {
          "id": "453",
          "question": "grupos",
          "solution": "groups",
          "additionText": "groups"
      },
      {
          "id": "454",
          "question": "miembros",
          "solution": "members",
          "additionText": "members"
      },
      {
          "id": "455",
          "question": "ninguna",
          "solution": "none",
          "additionText": "none"
      },
      {
          "id": "456",
          "question": "existe",
          "solution": "exists",
          "additionText": "exists"
      },
      {
          "id": "457",
          "question": "cara",
          "solution": "face",
          "additionText": "face"
      },
      {
          "id": "458",
          "question": "edad",
          "solution": "age",
          "additionText": "age"
      },
      {
          "id": "459",
          "question": "etc",
          "solution": "etc",
          "additionText": "etc"
      },
      {
          "id": "460",
          "question": "movimiento",
          "solution": "movement",
          "additionText": "movement"
      },
      {
          "id": "461",
          "question": "visto",
          "solution": "viewed",
          "additionText": "seen"
      },
      {
          "id": "462",
          "question": "llegó",
          "solution": "arrive",
          "additionText": "reached"
      },
      {
          "id": "463",
          "question": "puntos",
          "solution": "points",
          "additionText": "points"
      },
      {
          "id": "464",
          "question": "actividad",
          "solution": "activity",
          "additionText": "activity"
      },
      {
          "id": "465",
          "question": "bueno",
          "solution": "Okay",
          "additionText": "good"
      },
      {
          "id": "466",
          "question": "uso",
          "solution": "use",
          "additionText": "use"
      },
      {
          "id": "467",
          "question": "niño",
          "solution": "kid",
          "additionText": "child"
      },
      {
          "id": "468",
          "question": "difícil",
          "solution": "hard",
          "additionText": "difficult"
      },
      {
          "id": "469",
          "question": "joven",
          "solution": "young man",
          "additionText": "young"
      },
      {
          "id": "470",
          "question": "futuro",
          "solution": "future",
          "additionText": "future"
      },
      {
          "id": "471",
          "question": "aquellos",
          "solution": "those",
          "additionText": "those"
      },
      {
          "id": "472",
          "question": "mes",
          "solution": "month",
          "additionText": "month"
      },
      {
          "id": "473",
          "question": "pronto",
          "solution": "early",
          "additionText": "soon"
      },
      {
          "id": "474",
          "question": "soy",
          "solution": "am",
          "additionText": "I am"
      },
      {
          "id": "475",
          "question": "hacía",
          "solution": "toward",
          "additionText": "to"
      },
      {
          "id": "476",
          "question": "nuevos",
          "solution": "new",
          "additionText": "new"
      },
      {
          "id": "477",
          "question": "nuestros",
          "solution": "our",
          "additionText": "our"
      },
      {
          "id": "478",
          "question": "estaban",
          "solution": "were",
          "additionText": "were"
      },
      {
          "id": "479",
          "question": "posibilidad",
          "solution": "possibility",
          "additionText": "possibility"
      },
      {
          "id": "480",
          "question": "sigue",
          "solution": "go on",
          "additionText": "follow"
      },
      {
          "id": "481",
          "question": "cerca",
          "solution": "near",
          "additionText": "close"
      },
      {
          "id": "482",
          "question": "resultados",
          "solution": "results",
          "additionText": "results"
      },
      {
          "id": "483",
          "question": "educación",
          "solution": "education",
          "additionText": "education"
      },
      {
          "id": "484",
          "question": "atención",
          "solution": "attention",
          "additionText": "attention"
      },
      {
          "id": "485",
          "question": "gonzález",
          "solution": "gonzález",
          "additionText": "gonzalez"
      },
      {
          "id": "486",
          "question": "capacidad",
          "solution": "capacity",
          "additionText": "capacity"
      },
      {
          "id": "487",
          "question": "efecto",
          "solution": "effect",
          "additionText": "effect"
      },
      {
          "id": "488",
          "question": "necesario",
          "solution": "necessary",
          "additionText": "necessary"
      },
      {
          "id": "489",
          "question": "valor",
          "solution": "value",
          "additionText": "value"
      },
      {
          "id": "490",
          "question": "aire",
          "solution": "air",
          "additionText": "air"
      },
      {
          "id": "491",
          "question": "investigación",
          "solution": "investigation",
          "additionText": "research"
      },
      {
          "id": "492",
          "question": "siguiente",
          "solution": "following",
          "additionText": "next"
      },
      {
          "id": "493",
          "question": "figura",
          "solution": "figure",
          "additionText": "figure"
      },
      {
          "id": "494",
          "question": "central",
          "solution": "central",
          "additionText": "plant"
      },
      {
          "id": "495",
          "question": "comunidad",
          "solution": "community",
          "additionText": "community"
      },
      {
          "id": "496",
          "question": "necesidad",
          "solution": "need",
          "additionText": "need"
      },
      {
          "id": "497",
          "question": "serie",
          "solution": "Serie",
          "additionText": "series"
      },
      {
          "id": "498",
          "question": "organización",
          "solution": "organization",
          "additionText": "organization"
      },
      {
          "id": "499",
          "question": "nuevas",
          "solution": "news",
          "additionText": "new"
      },
      {
          "id": "500",
          "question": "calidad",
          "solution": "quality",
          "additionText": "quality"
      },
      {
          "id": "501",
          "question": "economía",
          "solution": "economy",
          "additionText": "economy"
      },
      {
          "id": "502",
          "question": "carácter",
          "solution": "character",
          "additionText": "character"
      },
      {
          "id": "503",
          "question": "jefe",
          "solution": "boss",
          "additionText": "boss"
      },
      {
          "id": "504",
          "question": "estamos",
          "solution": "we're",
          "additionText": "we are"
      },
      {
          "id": "505",
          "question": "prensa",
          "solution": "press",
          "additionText": "press"
      },
      {
          "id": "506",
          "question": "control",
          "solution": "control",
          "additionText": "control"
      },
      {
          "id": "507",
          "question": "sociales",
          "solution": "social",
          "additionText": "social"
      },
      {
          "id": "508",
          "question": "universidad",
          "solution": "college",
          "additionText": "university"
      },
      {
          "id": "509",
          "question": "militar",
          "solution": "military",
          "additionText": "military"
      },
      {
          "id": "510",
          "question": "cabo",
          "solution": "cape",
          "additionText": "corporal"
      },
      {
          "id": "511",
          "question": "diez",
          "solution": "ten",
          "additionText": "ten"
      },
      {
          "id": "512",
          "question": "fuerzas",
          "solution": "forces",
          "additionText": "forces"
      },
      {
          "id": "513",
          "question": "congreso",
          "solution": "congress",
          "additionText": "congress"
      },
      {
          "id": "514",
          "question": "ésta",
          "solution": "is",
          "additionText": "this"
      },
      {
          "id": "515",
          "question": "hijos",
          "solution": "sons",
          "additionText": "children"
      },
      {
          "id": "516",
          "question": "justicia",
          "solution": "Justice",
          "additionText": "justice"
      },
      {
          "id": "517",
          "question": "mundial",
          "solution": "world",
          "additionText": "world"
      },
      {
          "id": "518",
          "question": "dólares",
          "solution": "Dollars",
          "additionText": "dollars"
      },
      {
          "id": "519",
          "question": "juego",
          "solution": "play",
          "additionText": "gambling"
      },
      {
          "id": "520",
          "question": "económica",
          "solution": "economic",
          "additionText": "economic"
      },
      {
          "id": "521",
          "question": "políticos",
          "solution": "politicians",
          "additionText": "politicians"
      },
      {
          "id": "522",
          "question": "duda",
          "solution": "doubt",
          "additionText": "doubt"
      },
      {
          "id": "523",
          "question": "recursos",
          "solution": "resources",
          "additionText": "resources"
      },
      {
          "id": "524",
          "question": "pública",
          "solution": "public",
          "additionText": "public"
      },
      {
          "id": "525",
          "question": "crisis",
          "solution": "crisis",
          "additionText": "crisis"
      },
      {
          "id": "526",
          "question": "próximo",
          "solution": "next",
          "additionText": "next"
      },
      {
          "id": "527",
          "question": "tenemos",
          "solution": "we have",
          "additionText": "we have"
      },
      {
          "id": "528",
          "question": "decisión",
          "solution": "decision",
          "additionText": "decision"
      },
      {
          "id": "529",
          "question": "varias",
          "solution": "several",
          "additionText": "several"
      },
      {
          "id": "530",
          "question": "popular",
          "solution": "popular",
          "additionText": "popular"
      },
      {
          "id": "531",
          "question": "tenido",
          "solution": "Dyed",
          "additionText": "had"
      },
      {
          "id": "532",
          "question": "apenas",
          "solution": "barely",
          "additionText": "just"
      },
      {
          "id": "533",
          "question": "época",
          "solution": "epoch",
          "additionText": "time"
      },
      {
          "id": "534",
          "question": "banco",
          "solution": "Bank",
          "additionText": "bank"
      },
      {
          "id": "535",
          "question": "presente",
          "solution": "Present",
          "additionText": "present"
      },
      {
          "id": "536",
          "question": "menor",
          "solution": "less",
          "additionText": "minor"
      },
      {
          "id": "537",
          "question": "quiero",
          "solution": "I want",
          "additionText": "I want"
      },
      {
          "id": "538",
          "question": "pasar",
          "solution": "happen",
          "additionText": "pass"
      },
      {
          "id": "539",
          "question": "resultado",
          "solution": "result",
          "additionText": "result"
      },
      {
          "id": "540",
          "question": "televisión",
          "solution": "TV",
          "additionText": "television"
      },
      {
          "id": "541",
          "question": "encuentra",
          "solution": "finds",
          "additionText": "find"
      },
      {
          "id": "542",
          "question": "gracias",
          "solution": "Thank you",
          "additionText": "thank you"
      },
      {
          "id": "543",
          "question": "ministerio",
          "solution": "ministry",
          "additionText": "ministry"
      },
      {
          "id": "544",
          "question": "conjunto",
          "solution": "set",
          "additionText": "set"
      },
      {
          "id": "545",
          "question": "defensa",
          "solution": "defending",
          "additionText": "defense"
      },
      {
          "id": "546",
          "question": "alguien",
          "solution": "someone",
          "additionText": "someone"
      },
      {
          "id": "547",
          "question": "queda",
          "solution": "remains",
          "additionText": "is"
      },
      {
          "id": "548",
          "question": "hacen",
          "solution": "make",
          "additionText": "make"
      },
      {
          "id": "549",
          "question": "pasa",
          "solution": "happens",
          "additionText": "pass"
      },
      {
          "id": "550",
          "question": "resto",
          "solution": "rest",
          "additionText": "rest"
      },
      {
          "id": "551",
          "question": "causa",
          "solution": "cause",
          "additionText": "cause"
      },
      {
          "id": "552",
          "question": "seguir",
          "solution": "follow, continue",
          "additionText": "follow"
      },
      {
          "id": "553",
          "question": "allá",
          "solution": "there",
          "additionText": "there"
      },
      {
          "id": "554",
          "question": "palabra",
          "solution": "word",
          "additionText": "word"
      },
      {
          "id": "555",
          "question": "voy",
          "solution": "go",
          "additionText": "go"
      },
      {
          "id": "556",
          "question": "cuya",
          "solution": "which",
          "additionText": "whose"
      },
      {
          "id": "557",
          "question": "vamos",
          "solution": "come on",
          "additionText": "go"
      },
      {
          "id": "558",
          "question": "mar",
          "solution": "sea",
          "additionText": "sea"
      },
      {
          "id": "559",
          "question": "estudios",
          "solution": "studies",
          "additionText": "studies"
      },
      {
          "id": "560",
          "question": "derechos",
          "solution": "Rights",
          "additionText": "rights"
      },
      {
          "id": "561",
          "question": "importancia",
          "solution": "importance",
          "additionText": "importance"
      },
      {
          "id": "562",
          "question": "cuales",
          "solution": "which",
          "additionText": "which"
      },
      {
          "id": "563",
          "question": "contrario",
          "solution": "contrary",
          "additionText": "contrary"
      },
      {
          "id": "564",
          "question": "manuel",
          "solution": "Manuel",
          "additionText": "manuel"
      },
      {
          "id": "565",
          "question": "garcía",
          "solution": "garcía",
          "additionText": "garcia"
      },
      {
          "id": "566",
          "question": "fuerte",
          "solution": "strong",
          "additionText": "strong"
      },
      {
          "id": "567",
          "question": "sol",
          "solution": "Sun",
          "additionText": "sun"
      },
      {
          "id": "568",
          "question": "jóvenes",
          "solution": "youths",
          "additionText": "young people"
      },
      {
          "id": "569",
          "question": "apoyo",
          "solution": "support for",
          "additionText": "support"
      },
      {
          "id": "570",
          "question": "habría",
          "solution": "there would be",
          "additionText": "there would be"
      },
      {
          "id": "571",
          "question": "civil",
          "solution": "civil",
          "additionText": "civil"
      },
      {
          "id": "572",
          "question": "miguel",
          "solution": "Michael",
          "additionText": "miguel"
      },
      {
          "id": "573",
          "question": "pedro",
          "solution": "Peter",
          "additionText": "pedro"
      },
      {
          "id": "574",
          "question": "partidos",
          "solution": "matches",
          "additionText": "parties"
      },
      {
          "id": "575",
          "question": "libre",
          "solution": "free",
          "additionText": "free"
      },
      {
          "id": "576",
          "question": "fuentes",
          "solution": "sources",
          "additionText": "sources"
      },
      {
          "id": "577",
          "question": "administración",
          "solution": "management",
          "additionText": "administration"
      },
      {
          "id": "578",
          "question": "común",
          "solution": "common",
          "additionText": "common"
      },
      {
          "id": "579",
          "question": "dejar",
          "solution": "let",
          "additionText": "leave"
      },
      {
          "id": "580",
          "question": "cine",
          "solution": "movies",
          "additionText": "cinema"
      },
      {
          "id": "581",
          "question": "salir",
          "solution": "get out",
          "additionText": "leave"
      },
      {
          "id": "582",
          "question": "comunicación",
          "solution": "communication",
          "additionText": "communication"
      },
      {
          "id": "583",
          "question": "b",
          "solution": "b",
          "additionText": "b"
      },
      {
          "id": "584",
          "question": "experiencia",
          "solution": "experience",
          "additionText": "experience"
      },
      {
          "id": "585",
          "question": "demasiado",
          "solution": "too",
          "additionText": "too much"
      },
      {
          "id": "586",
          "question": "plan",
          "solution": "plan",
          "additionText": "plan"
      },
      {
          "id": "587",
          "question": "respuesta",
          "solution": "answer",
          "additionText": "response"
      },
      {
          "id": "588",
          "question": "energía",
          "solution": "Energy",
          "additionText": "energy"
      },
      {
          "id": "589",
          "question": "izquierda",
          "solution": "left",
          "additionText": "left"
      },
      {
          "id": "590",
          "question": "función",
          "solution": "function",
          "additionText": "function"
      },
      {
          "id": "591",
          "question": "principal",
          "solution": "principal",
          "additionText": "main"
      },
      {
          "id": "592",
          "question": "superior",
          "solution": "higher",
          "additionText": "top"
      },
      {
          "id": "593",
          "question": "naturaleza",
          "solution": "nature",
          "additionText": "nature"
      },
      {
          "id": "594",
          "question": "podemos",
          "solution": "we can",
          "additionText": "we can"
      },
      {
          "id": "595",
          "question": "unión",
          "solution": "Union",
          "additionText": "link"
      },
      {
          "id": "596",
          "question": "especialmente",
          "solution": "especially",
          "additionText": "especially"
      },
      {
          "id": "597",
          "question": "rey",
          "solution": "King",
          "additionText": "king"
      },
      {
          "id": "598",
          "question": "domingo",
          "solution": "Sunday",
          "additionText": "Sunday"
      },
      {
          "id": "599",
          "question": "favor",
          "solution": "favor",
          "additionText": "please"
      },
      {
          "id": "600",
          "question": "cantidad",
          "solution": "amount",
          "additionText": "amount"
      },
      {
          "id": "601",
          "question": "elecciones",
          "solution": "elections",
          "additionText": "elections"
      },
      {
          "id": "602",
          "question": "clase",
          "solution": "class",
          "additionText": "class"
      },
      {
          "id": "603",
          "question": "productos",
          "solution": "products",
          "additionText": "products"
      },
      {
          "id": "604",
          "question": "españoles",
          "solution": "Spanish people",
          "additionText": "Spanish"
      },
      {
          "id": "605",
          "question": "conocer",
          "solution": "know",
          "additionText": "visit"
      },
      {
          "id": "606",
          "question": "teatro",
          "solution": "theater",
          "additionText": "theater"
      },
      {
          "id": "607",
          "question": "importantes",
          "solution": "important",
          "additionText": "important"
      },
      {
          "id": "608",
          "question": "evitar",
          "solution": "to avoid",
          "additionText": "avoid"
      },
      {
          "id": "609",
          "question": "color",
          "solution": "colour",
          "additionText": "color"
      },
      {
          "id": "610",
          "question": "actividades",
          "solution": "activities",
          "additionText": "activities"
      },
      {
          "id": "611",
          "question": "mesa",
          "solution": "desk",
          "additionText": "table"
      },
      {
          "id": "612",
          "question": "p",
          "solution": "p",
          "additionText": "p"
      },
      {
          "id": "613",
          "question": "decía",
          "solution": "He said",
          "additionText": "said"
      },
      {
          "id": "614",
          "question": "cuyo",
          "solution": "whose",
          "additionText": "whose"
      },
      {
          "id": "615",
          "question": "debido",
          "solution": "due",
          "additionText": "due"
      },
      {
          "id": "616",
          "question": "alta",
          "solution": "high",
          "additionText": "high"
      },
      {
          "id": "617",
          "question": "francisco",
          "solution": "Francisco",
          "additionText": "francisco"
      },
      {
          "id": "618",
          "question": "secretario",
          "solution": "secretary",
          "additionText": "secretary"
      },
      {
          "id": "619",
          "question": "objeto",
          "solution": "object",
          "additionText": "object"
      },
      {
          "id": "620",
          "question": "quizá",
          "solution": "maybe",
          "additionText": "maybe"
      },
      {
          "id": "621",
          "question": "posición",
          "solution": "position",
          "additionText": "position"
      },
      {
          "id": "622",
          "question": "parecía",
          "solution": "looked like",
          "additionText": "it seemed"
      },
      {
          "id": "623",
          "question": "natural",
          "solution": "natural",
          "additionText": "natural"
      },
      {
          "id": "624",
          "question": "elementos",
          "solution": "elements",
          "additionText": "elements"
      },
      {
          "id": "625",
          "question": "hubo",
          "solution": "was",
          "additionText": "there was"
      },
      {
          "id": "626",
          "question": "objetivo",
          "solution": "target",
          "additionText": "target"
      },
      {
          "id": "627",
          "question": "formas",
          "solution": "shapes",
          "additionText": "forms"
      },
      {
          "id": "628",
          "question": "única",
          "solution": "only",
          "additionText": "only"
      },
      {
          "id": "629",
          "question": "pueda",
          "solution": "can",
          "additionText": "can"
      },
      {
          "id": "630",
          "question": "origen",
          "solution": "source",
          "additionText": "origin"
      },
      {
          "id": "631",
          "question": "blanco",
          "solution": "White",
          "additionText": "target"
      },
      {
          "id": "632",
          "question": "mismos",
          "solution": "same",
          "additionText": "same"
      },
      {
          "id": "633",
          "question": "lleva",
          "solution": "carries",
          "additionText": "carries"
      },
      {
          "id": "634",
          "question": "económico",
          "solution": "economic",
          "additionText": "economic"
      },
      {
          "id": "635",
          "question": "opinión",
          "solution": "opinion",
          "additionText": "opinion"
      },
      {
          "id": "636",
          "question": "ayuda",
          "solution": "help",
          "additionText": "help"
      },
      {
          "id": "637",
          "question": "oficial",
          "solution": "official",
          "additionText": "official"
      },
      {
          "id": "638",
          "question": "silencio",
          "solution": "silence",
          "additionText": "silence"
      },
      {
          "id": "639",
          "question": "buenos",
          "solution": "good",
          "additionText": "good"
      },
      {
          "id": "640",
          "question": "pensar",
          "solution": "to think",
          "additionText": "think"
      },
      {
          "id": "641",
          "question": "república",
          "solution": "republic",
          "additionText": "republic"
      },
      {
          "id": "642",
          "question": "dónde",
          "solution": "where",
          "additionText": "where"
      },
      {
          "id": "643",
          "question": "sangre",
          "solution": "blood",
          "additionText": "blood"
      },
      {
          "id": "644",
          "question": "encuentro",
          "solution": "meeting",
          "additionText": "I find"
      },
      {
          "id": "645",
          "question": "siquiera",
          "solution": "at least",
          "additionText": "even"
      },
      {
          "id": "646",
          "question": "autor",
          "solution": "Author",
          "additionText": "author"
      },
      {
          "id": "647",
          "question": "reunión",
          "solution": "meeting",
          "additionText": "meeting"
      },
      {
          "id": "648",
          "question": "haciendo",
          "solution": "doing",
          "additionText": "making"
      },
      {
          "id": "649",
          "question": "suelo",
          "solution": "floor",
          "additionText": "ground"
      },
      {
          "id": "650",
          "question": "muestra",
          "solution": "sample",
          "additionText": "sample"
      },
      {
          "id": "651",
          "question": "viejo",
          "solution": "old",
          "additionText": "old"
      },
      {
          "id": "652",
          "question": "encima",
          "solution": "above",
          "additionText": "over"
      },
      {
          "id": "653",
          "question": "resulta",
          "solution": "result",
          "additionText": "turns out"
      },
      {
          "id": "654",
          "question": "tomar",
          "solution": "take",
          "additionText": "take"
      },
      {
          "id": "655",
          "question": "bastante",
          "solution": "Quite",
          "additionText": "quite a lot"
      },
      {
          "id": "656",
          "question": "siete",
          "solution": "seven",
          "additionText": "seven"
      },
      {
          "id": "657",
          "question": "lucha",
          "solution": "struggle",
          "additionText": "fight"
      },
      {
          "id": "658",
          "question": "pudo",
          "solution": "could",
          "additionText": "could"
      },
      {
          "id": "659",
          "question": "amigos",
          "solution": "friends",
          "additionText": "friends"
      },
      {
          "id": "660",
          "question": "línea",
          "solution": "line",
          "additionText": "line"
      },
      {
          "id": "661",
          "question": "sur",
          "solution": "south",
          "additionText": "south"
      },
      {
          "id": "662",
          "question": "pocos",
          "solution": "few",
          "additionText": "few"
      },
      {
          "id": "663",
          "question": "medidas",
          "solution": "measures",
          "additionText": "measures"
      },
      {
          "id": "664",
          "question": "norte",
          "solution": "North",
          "additionText": "north"
      },
      {
          "id": "665",
          "question": "partes",
          "solution": "parts",
          "additionText": "parts"
      },
      {
          "id": "666",
          "question": "iglesia",
          "solution": "church",
          "additionText": "church"
      },
      {
          "id": "667",
          "question": "tratamiento",
          "solution": "treatment",
          "additionText": "treatment"
      },
      {
          "id": "668",
          "question": "existencia",
          "solution": "existence",
          "additionText": "existence"
      },
      {
          "id": "669",
          "question": "cargo",
          "solution": "position",
          "additionText": "charge"
      },
      {
          "id": "670",
          "question": "grande",
          "solution": "big",
          "additionText": "grande"
      },
      {
          "id": "671",
          "question": "américa",
          "solution": "America",
          "additionText": "america"
      },
      {
          "id": "672",
          "question": "boca",
          "solution": "mouth",
          "additionText": "boca"
      },
      {
          "id": "673",
          "question": "plaza",
          "solution": "Plaza",
          "additionText": "plaza"
      },
      {
          "id": "674",
          "question": "pie",
          "solution": "foot",
          "additionText": "pie"
      },
      {
          "id": "675",
          "question": "trabajadores",
          "solution": "workers",
          "additionText": "workers"
      },
      {
          "id": "676",
          "question": "poner",
          "solution": "put",
          "additionText": "put"
      },
      {
          "id": "677",
          "question": "existen",
          "solution": "exist",
          "additionText": "there are"
      },
      {
          "id": "678",
          "question": "viene",
          "solution": "comes",
          "additionText": "comes"
      },
      {
          "id": "679",
          "question": "permite",
          "solution": "It allows",
          "additionText": "allows"
      },
      {
          "id": "680",
          "question": "análisis",
          "solution": "analysis",
          "additionText": "analysis"
      },
      {
          "id": "681",
          "question": "argentina",
          "solution": "Argentina",
          "additionText": "argentina"
      },
      {
          "id": "682",
          "question": "acto",
          "solution": "act",
          "additionText": "act"
      },
      {
          "id": "683",
          "question": "hechos",
          "solution": "facts",
          "additionText": "facts"
      },
      {
          "id": "684",
          "question": "tiempos",
          "solution": "time",
          "additionText": "times"
      },
      {
          "id": "685",
          "question": "políticas",
          "solution": "policies",
          "additionText": "policies"
      },
      {
          "id": "686",
          "question": "radio",
          "solution": "radio",
          "additionText": "radio"
      },
      {
          "id": "687",
          "question": "puedo",
          "solution": "may l",
          "additionText": "I can"
      },
      {
          "id": "688",
          "question": "crecimiento",
          "solution": "growth",
          "additionText": "growth"
      },
      {
          "id": "689",
          "question": "francia",
          "solution": "France",
          "additionText": "france"
      },
      {
          "id": "690",
          "question": "compañía",
          "solution": "company",
          "additionText": "company"
      },
      {
          "id": "691",
          "question": "amigo",
          "solution": "friend",
          "additionText": "friend"
      },
      {
          "id": "692",
          "question": "autoridades",
          "solution": "authorities",
          "additionText": "authorities"
      },
      {
          "id": "693",
          "question": "realizar",
          "solution": "perform",
          "additionText": "conduct"
      },
      {
          "id": "694",
          "question": "acciones",
          "solution": "Actions",
          "additionText": "actions"
      },
      {
          "id": "695",
          "question": "padres",
          "solution": "fathers",
          "additionText": "parents"
      },
      {
          "id": "696",
          "question": "diario",
          "solution": "daily",
          "additionText": "diary"
      },
      {
          "id": "697",
          "question": "ve",
          "solution": "go",
          "additionText": "see"
      },
      {
          "id": "698",
          "question": "derecha",
          "solution": "right",
          "additionText": "right"
      },
      {
          "id": "699",
          "question": "ambiente",
          "solution": "ambient",
          "additionText": "environment"
      },
      {
          "id": "700",
          "question": "i",
          "solution": "i",
          "additionText": "i"
      },
      {
          "id": "701",
          "question": "habrá",
          "solution": "there will be",
          "additionText": "there will be"
      },
      {
          "id": "702",
          "question": "precisamente",
          "solution": "precisely",
          "additionText": "precisely"
      },
      {
          "id": "703",
          "question": "enfermedad",
          "solution": "disease",
          "additionText": "disease"
      },
      {
          "id": "704",
          "question": "especie",
          "solution": "species",
          "additionText": "species"
      },
      {
          "id": "705",
          "question": "ejército",
          "solution": "army",
          "additionText": "army"
      },
      {
          "id": "706",
          "question": "santa",
          "solution": "St.",
          "additionText": "holy"
      },
      {
          "id": "707",
          "question": "cambios",
          "solution": "changes",
          "additionText": "changes"
      },
      {
          "id": "708",
          "question": "río",
          "solution": "River",
          "additionText": "river"
      },
      {
          "id": "709",
          "question": "sabía",
          "solution": "I knew",
          "additionText": "knew"
      },
      {
          "id": "710",
          "question": "seguro",
          "solution": "insurance",
          "additionText": "insurance"
      },
      {
          "id": "711",
          "question": "espera",
          "solution": "waiting",
          "additionText": "wait"
      },
      {
          "id": "712",
          "question": "momentos",
          "solution": "moments",
          "additionText": "moments"
      },
      {
          "id": "713",
          "question": "viaje",
          "solution": "travel",
          "additionText": "trip"
      },
      {
          "id": "714",
          "question": "quería",
          "solution": "wanted",
          "additionText": "wanted"
      },
      {
          "id": "715",
          "question": "ocho",
          "solution": "eight",
          "additionText": "eight"
      },
      {
          "id": "716",
          "question": "vivir",
          "solution": "to live",
          "additionText": "live"
      },
      {
          "id": "717",
          "question": "región",
          "solution": "region",
          "additionText": "region"
      },
      {
          "id": "718",
          "question": "formación",
          "solution": "training",
          "additionText": "training"
      },
      {
          "id": "719",
          "question": "escuela",
          "solution": "school",
          "additionText": "school"
      },
      {
          "id": "720",
          "question": "cuarto",
          "solution": "room",
          "additionText": "fourth"
      },
      {
          "id": "721",
          "question": "valores",
          "solution": "values",
          "additionText": "values"
      },
      {
          "id": "722",
          "question": "quedó",
          "solution": "it was",
          "additionText": "remained"
      },
      {
          "id": "723",
          "question": "participación",
          "solution": "participation",
          "additionText": "participation"
      },
      {
          "id": "724",
          "question": "éxito",
          "solution": "success",
          "additionText": "success"
      },
      {
          "id": "725",
          "question": "baja",
          "solution": "low",
          "additionText": "low"
      },
      {
          "id": "726",
          "question": "artículo",
          "solution": "Article",
          "additionText": "article"
      },
      {
          "id": "727",
          "question": "principales",
          "solution": "main",
          "additionText": "main"
      },
      {
          "id": "728",
          "question": "fernando",
          "solution": "fernando",
          "additionText": "fernando"
      },
      {
          "id": "729",
          "question": "metros",
          "solution": "meters",
          "additionText": "meters"
      },
      {
          "id": "730",
          "question": "marcha",
          "solution": "March",
          "additionText": "march"
      },
      {
          "id": "731",
          "question": "régimen",
          "solution": "regime",
          "additionText": "regime"
      },
      {
          "id": "732",
          "question": "consecuencia",
          "solution": "consequence",
          "additionText": "consequence"
      },
      {
          "id": "733",
          "question": "conocimiento",
          "solution": "knowledge",
          "additionText": "awareness"
      },
      {
          "id": "734",
          "question": "corazón",
          "solution": "heart",
          "additionText": "heart"
      },
      {
          "id": "735",
          "question": "campaña",
          "solution": "Bell",
          "additionText": "campaign"
      },
      {
          "id": "736",
          "question": "estructura",
          "solution": "structure",
          "additionText": "structure"
      },
      {
          "id": "737",
          "question": "efectos",
          "solution": "effects",
          "additionText": "effects"
      },
      {
          "id": "738",
          "question": "finalmente",
          "solution": "Finally",
          "additionText": "finally"
      },
      {
          "id": "739",
          "question": "modelo",
          "solution": "model",
          "additionText": "template"
      },
      {
          "id": "740",
          "question": "carta",
          "solution": "letter",
          "additionText": "charter"
      },
      {
          "id": "741",
          "question": "construcción",
          "solution": "construction",
          "additionText": "constr"
      },
      {
          "id": "742",
          "question": "médico",
          "solution": "doctor",
          "additionText": "doctor"
      },
      {
          "id": "743",
          "question": "miedo",
          "solution": "afraid",
          "additionText": "fear"
      },
      {
          "id": "744",
          "question": "mayores",
          "solution": "greater",
          "additionText": "seniors"
      },
      {
          "id": "745",
          "question": "entrada",
          "solution": "entrance",
          "additionText": "entry"
      },
      {
          "id": "746",
          "question": "humanos",
          "solution": "humans",
          "additionText": "humans"
      },
      {
          "id": "747",
          "question": "sean",
          "solution": "are",
          "additionText": "be"
      },
      {
          "id": "748",
          "question": "actitud",
          "solution": "attitude",
          "additionText": "attitude"
      },
      {
          "id": "749",
          "question": "deja",
          "solution": "leaves",
          "additionText": "leave"
      },
      {
          "id": "750",
          "question": "dejó",
          "solution": "let",
          "additionText": "let"
      },
      {
          "id": "751",
          "question": "d",
          "solution": "d",
          "additionText": "d"
      },
      {
          "id": "752",
          "question": "llevar",
          "solution": "bring",
          "additionText": "wear"
      },
      {
          "id": "753",
          "question": "negro",
          "solution": "black",
          "additionText": "black"
      },
      {
          "id": "754",
          "question": "texto",
          "solution": "text",
          "additionText": "text"
      },
      {
          "id": "755",
          "question": "mitad",
          "solution": "half",
          "additionText": "half"
      },
      {
          "id": "756",
          "question": "estuvo",
          "solution": "he was",
          "additionText": "was"
      },
      {
          "id": "757",
          "question": "alrededor",
          "solution": "around",
          "additionText": "about"
      },
      {
          "id": "758",
          "question": "acerca",
          "solution": "about",
          "additionText": "about"
      },
      {
          "id": "759",
          "question": "peso",
          "solution": "weight",
          "additionText": "weight"
      },
      {
          "id": "760",
          "question": "humano",
          "solution": "human",
          "additionText": "human"
      },
      {
          "id": "761",
          "question": "pequeño",
          "solution": "little",
          "additionText": "small"
      },
      {
          "id": "762",
          "question": "fecha",
          "solution": "date",
          "additionText": "date"
      },
      {
          "id": "763",
          "question": "serán",
          "solution": "will be",
          "additionText": "will be"
      },
      {
          "id": "764",
          "question": "doctor",
          "solution": "doctor",
          "additionText": "doctor"
      },
      {
          "id": "765",
          "question": "ideas",
          "solution": "Ideas",
          "additionText": "ideas"
      },
      {
          "id": "766",
          "question": "vino",
          "solution": "wine",
          "additionText": "wine"
      },
      {
          "id": "767",
          "question": "materia",
          "solution": "subject",
          "additionText": "matter"
      },
      {
          "id": "768",
          "question": "llega",
          "solution": "arrives",
          "additionText": "arrives"
      },
      {
          "id": "769",
          "question": "carrera",
          "solution": "career",
          "additionText": "career"
      },
      {
          "id": "770",
          "question": "cierta",
          "solution": "some",
          "additionText": "certain"
      },
      {
          "id": "771",
          "question": "sola",
          "solution": "alone",
          "additionText": "only"
      },
      {
          "id": "772",
          "question": "psoe",
          "solution": "psoe",
          "additionText": "psoe"
      },
      {
          "id": "773",
          "question": "lejos",
          "solution": "far",
          "additionText": "far"
      },
      {
          "id": "774",
          "question": "juez",
          "solution": "judge",
          "additionText": "judge"
      },
      {
          "id": "775",
          "question": "características",
          "solution": "characteristics",
          "additionText": "characteristics"
      },
      {
          "id": "776",
          "question": "riesgo",
          "solution": "risk",
          "additionText": "risk"
      },
      {
          "id": "777",
          "question": "fácil",
          "solution": "easy",
          "additionText": "easy"
      },
      {
          "id": "778",
          "question": "diferencia",
          "solution": "difference",
          "additionText": "difference"
      },
      {
          "id": "779",
          "question": "cultural",
          "solution": "cultural",
          "additionText": "cultural"
      },
      {
          "id": "780",
          "question": "libros",
          "solution": "books",
          "additionText": "books"
      },
      {
          "id": "781",
          "question": "práctica",
          "solution": "practice",
          "additionText": "practice"
      },
      {
          "id": "782",
          "question": "mayo",
          "solution": "May",
          "additionText": "may"
      },
      {
          "id": "783",
          "question": "nuestras",
          "solution": "our",
          "additionText": "our"
      },
      {
          "id": "784",
          "question": "programas",
          "solution": "programs",
          "additionText": "programs"
      },
      {
          "id": "785",
          "question": "memoria",
          "solution": "memory",
          "additionText": "memory"
      },
      {
          "id": "786",
          "question": "llegado",
          "solution": "arrived",
          "additionText": "arrived"
      },
      {
          "id": "787",
          "question": "plazo",
          "solution": "term",
          "additionText": "deadline"
      },
      {
          "id": "788",
          "question": "expresión",
          "solution": "expression",
          "additionText": "expression"
      },
      {
          "id": "789",
          "question": "diciembre",
          "solution": "December",
          "additionText": "december"
      },
      {
          "id": "790",
          "question": "mantener",
          "solution": "keep",
          "additionText": "maintain"
      },
      {
          "id": "791",
          "question": "enero",
          "solution": "January",
          "additionText": "January"
      },
      {
          "id": "792",
          "question": "volver",
          "solution": "return",
          "additionText": "go back to"
      },
      {
          "id": "793",
          "question": "cuadro",
          "solution": "picture",
          "additionText": "table"
      },
      {
          "id": "794",
          "question": "producto",
          "solution": "product",
          "additionText": "product"
      },
      {
          "id": "795",
          "question": "produce",
          "solution": "produces",
          "additionText": "produced"
      },
      {
          "id": "796",
          "question": "europea",
          "solution": "European",
          "additionText": "european"
      },
      {
          "id": "797",
          "question": "conciencia",
          "solution": "conscience",
          "additionText": "conscience"
      },
      {
          "id": "798",
          "question": "tenían",
          "solution": "They had",
          "additionText": "had"
      },
      {
          "id": "799",
          "question": "atrás",
          "solution": "behind",
          "additionText": "back"
      },
      {
          "id": "800",
          "question": "felipe",
          "solution": "felipe",
          "additionText": "Philip"
      },
      {
          "id": "801",
          "question": "creación",
          "solution": "creation",
          "additionText": "creation"
      },
      {
          "id": "802",
          "question": "chile",
          "solution": "Chile",
          "additionText": "chile"
      },
      {
          "id": "803",
          "question": "precio",
          "solution": "price",
          "additionText": "price"
      },
      {
          "id": "804",
          "question": "película",
          "solution": "movie",
          "additionText": "film"
      },
      {
          "id": "805",
          "question": "puerto",
          "solution": "port",
          "additionText": "port"
      },
      {
          "id": "806",
          "question": "fuego",
          "solution": "fire",
          "additionText": "fire"
      },
      {
          "id": "807",
          "question": "cuestión",
          "solution": "question",
          "additionText": "issue"
      },
      {
          "id": "808",
          "question": "pasó",
          "solution": "I pass",
          "additionText": "happened"
      },
      {
          "id": "809",
          "question": "costa",
          "solution": "coast",
          "additionText": "coast"
      },
      {
          "id": "810",
          "question": "supuesto",
          "solution": "supposed",
          "additionText": "alleged"
      },
      {
          "id": "811",
          "question": "local",
          "solution": "local",
          "additionText": "local"
      },
      {
          "id": "812",
          "question": "habla",
          "solution": "speaks",
          "additionText": "speech"
      },
      {
          "id": "813",
          "question": "aspectos",
          "solution": "aspects",
          "additionText": "aspects"
      },
      {
          "id": "814",
          "question": "cuba",
          "solution": "Cuba",
          "additionText": "cuba"
      },
      {
          "id": "815",
          "question": "sala",
          "solution": "living room",
          "additionText": "room"
      },
      {
          "id": "816",
          "question": "cámara",
          "solution": "camera",
          "additionText": "camera"
      },
      {
          "id": "817",
          "question": "vuelta",
          "solution": "return",
          "additionText": "return"
      },
      {
          "id": "818",
          "question": "vía",
          "solution": "via",
          "additionText": "via"
      },
      {
          "id": "819",
          "question": "mirada",
          "solution": "look",
          "additionText": "look"
      },
      {
          "id": "820",
          "question": "mejores",
          "solution": "top",
          "additionText": "best"
      },
      {
          "id": "821",
          "question": "informe",
          "solution": "report",
          "additionText": "report"
      },
      {
          "id": "822",
          "question": "unidad",
          "solution": "Unit",
          "additionText": "unit"
      },
      {
          "id": "823",
          "question": "distintos",
          "solution": "different",
          "additionText": "different"
      },
      {
          "id": "824",
          "question": "suerte",
          "solution": "lucky",
          "additionText": "luck"
      },
      {
          "id": "825",
          "question": "tales",
          "solution": "such",
          "additionText": "such"
      },
      {
          "id": "826",
          "question": "mira",
          "solution": "sight",
          "additionText": "see"
      },
      {
          "id": "827",
          "question": "llamado",
          "solution": "called",
          "additionText": "called"
      },
      {
          "id": "828",
          "question": "técnica",
          "solution": "technique",
          "additionText": "technique"
      },
      {
          "id": "829",
          "question": "título",
          "solution": "qualification",
          "additionText": "title"
      },
      {
          "id": "830",
          "question": "s",
          "solution": "s",
          "additionText": "s"
      },
      {
          "id": "831",
          "question": "principios",
          "solution": "beginning",
          "additionText": "principles"
      },
      {
          "id": "832",
          "question": "octubre",
          "solution": "October",
          "additionText": "October"
      },
      {
          "id": "833",
          "question": "volvió",
          "solution": "went back",
          "additionText": "returned"
      },
      {
          "id": "834",
          "question": "período",
          "solution": "period",
          "additionText": "period"
      },
      {
          "id": "835",
          "question": "g",
          "solution": "g",
          "additionText": "g"
      },
      {
          "id": "836",
          "question": "encontrar",
          "solution": "meet",
          "additionText": "find"
      },
      {
          "id": "837",
          "question": "democracia",
          "solution": "democracy",
          "additionText": "democracy"
      },
      {
          "id": "838",
          "question": "aumento",
          "solution": "increase",
          "additionText": "increase"
      },
      {
          "id": "839",
          "question": "fútbol",
          "solution": "soccer",
          "additionText": "soccer"
      },
      {
          "id": "840",
          "question": "prueba",
          "solution": "proof",
          "additionText": "test"
      },
      {
          "id": "841",
          "question": "consumo",
          "solution": "consumption",
          "additionText": "consumption"
      },
      {
          "id": "842",
          "question": "pese",
          "solution": "I weighed",
          "additionText": "despite"
      },
      {
          "id": "843",
          "question": "ocasiones",
          "solution": "occasions",
          "additionText": "occasions"
      },
      {
          "id": "844",
          "question": "exterior",
          "solution": "Exterior",
          "additionText": "outside"
      },
      {
          "id": "845",
          "question": "solución",
          "solution": "solution",
          "additionText": "solution"
      },
      {
          "id": "846",
          "question": "u",
          "solution": "or",
          "additionText": "u"
      },
      {
          "id": "847",
          "question": "hija",
          "solution": "daughter",
          "additionText": "daughter"
      },
      {
          "id": "848",
          "question": "sueño",
          "solution": "dream",
          "additionText": "dream"
      },
      {
          "id": "849",
          "question": "parís",
          "solution": "Paris",
          "additionText": "paris"
      },
      {
          "id": "850",
          "question": "capaz",
          "solution": "capable",
          "additionText": "able"
      },
      {
          "id": "851",
          "question": "ocasión",
          "solution": "chance",
          "additionText": "occasion"
      },
      {
          "id": "852",
          "question": "industria",
          "solution": "industry",
          "additionText": "industry"
      },
      {
          "id": "853",
          "question": "adelante",
          "solution": "ahead",
          "additionText": "forward"
      },
      {
          "id": "854",
          "question": "salida",
          "solution": "Exit",
          "additionText": "exit"
      },
      {
          "id": "855",
          "question": "ciencia",
          "solution": "science",
          "additionText": "science"
      },
      {
          "id": "856",
          "question": "asunto",
          "solution": "business",
          "additionText": "subject"
      },
      {
          "id": "857",
          "question": "asociación",
          "solution": "association",
          "additionText": "association"
      },
      {
          "id": "858",
          "question": "puso",
          "solution": "put",
          "additionText": "put"
      },
      {
          "id": "859",
          "question": "intereses",
          "solution": "interests",
          "additionText": "interests"
      },
      {
          "id": "860",
          "question": "oro",
          "solution": "gold",
          "additionText": "gold"
      },
      {
          "id": "861",
          "question": "podrá",
          "solution": "you can",
          "additionText": "you may"
      },
      {
          "id": "862",
          "question": "pregunta",
          "solution": "question",
          "additionText": "question"
      },
      {
          "id": "863",
          "question": "oposición",
          "solution": "opposition",
          "additionText": "opposition"
      },
      {
          "id": "864",
          "question": "entrar",
          "solution": "get in",
          "additionText": "enter"
      },
      {
          "id": "865",
          "question": "señora",
          "solution": "Lady",
          "additionText": "Mrs."
      },
      {
          "id": "866",
          "question": "señaló",
          "solution": "he pointed",
          "additionText": "pointed out"
      },
      {
          "id": "867",
          "question": "santiago",
          "solution": "Santiago",
          "additionText": "santiago"
      },
      {
          "id": "868",
          "question": "dolor",
          "solution": "pain",
          "additionText": "pain"
      },
      {
          "id": "869",
          "question": "zonas",
          "solution": "areas",
          "additionText": "zones"
      },
      {
          "id": "870",
          "question": "comercio",
          "solution": "trade",
          "additionText": "commerce"
      },
      {
          "id": "871",
          "question": "operación",
          "solution": "operation",
          "additionText": "operation"
      },
      {
          "id": "872",
          "question": "tribunal",
          "solution": "court",
          "additionText": "court"
      },
      {
          "id": "873",
          "question": "instituciones",
          "solution": "institutions",
          "additionText": "institutions"
      },
      {
          "id": "874",
          "question": "temas",
          "solution": "topics",
          "additionText": "issues"
      },
      {
          "id": "875",
          "question": "militares",
          "solution": "military",
          "additionText": "military"
      },
      {
          "id": "876",
          "question": "junio",
          "solution": "June",
          "additionText": "June"
      },
      {
          "id": "877",
          "question": "marco",
          "solution": "framework",
          "additionText": "framework"
      },
      {
          "id": "878",
          "question": "sectores",
          "solution": "sectors",
          "additionText": "sectors"
      },
      {
          "id": "879",
          "question": "hacerlo",
          "solution": "do it",
          "additionText": "make it"
      },
      {
          "id": "880",
          "question": "aspecto",
          "solution": "appearance",
          "additionText": "aspect"
      },
      {
          "id": "881",
          "question": "razones",
          "solution": "reasons",
          "additionText": "reasons"
      },
      {
          "id": "882",
          "question": "contenido",
          "solution": "contents",
          "additionText": "content"
      },
      {
          "id": "883",
          "question": "juicio",
          "solution": "judgment",
          "additionText": "judgment"
      },
      {
          "id": "884",
          "question": "electoral",
          "solution": "electoral",
          "additionText": "electoral"
      },
      {
          "id": "885",
          "question": "considera",
          "solution": "considers",
          "additionText": "considers"
      },
      {
          "id": "886",
          "question": "tendrá",
          "solution": "will have",
          "additionText": "will have"
      },
      {
          "id": "887",
          "question": "mucha",
          "solution": "a lot",
          "additionText": "much"
      },
      {
          "id": "888",
          "question": "voluntad",
          "solution": "Will",
          "additionText": "will"
      },
      {
          "id": "889",
          "question": "dicen",
          "solution": "say",
          "additionText": "say"
      },
      {
          "id": "890",
          "question": "recuerdo",
          "solution": "memory",
          "additionText": "reminder"
      },
      {
          "id": "891",
          "question": "socialista",
          "solution": "socialist",
          "additionText": "socialist"
      },
      {
          "id": "892",
          "question": "área",
          "solution": "area",
          "additionText": "area"
      },
      {
          "id": "893",
          "question": "aparece",
          "solution": "appear",
          "additionText": "appears"
      },
      {
          "id": "894",
          "question": "vio",
          "solution": "saw",
          "additionText": "saw"
      },
      {
          "id": "895",
          "question": "cama",
          "solution": "bed",
          "additionText": "bed"
      },
      {
          "id": "896",
          "question": "aun",
          "solution": "yet",
          "additionText": "even"
      },
      {
          "id": "897",
          "question": "presenta",
          "solution": "presents",
          "additionText": "presents"
      },
      {
          "id": "898",
          "question": "pp",
          "solution": "pp",
          "additionText": "pp"
      },
      {
          "id": "899",
          "question": "revolución",
          "solution": "revolution",
          "additionText": "revolution"
      },
      {
          "id": "900",
          "question": "busca",
          "solution": "search",
          "additionText": "search"
      },
      {
          "id": "901",
          "question": "abril",
          "solution": "April",
          "additionText": "april"
      },
      {
          "id": "902",
          "question": "rodríguez",
          "solution": "rodríguez",
          "additionText": "rodriguez"
      },
      {
          "id": "903",
          "question": "fiscal",
          "solution": "fiscal",
          "additionText": "prosecutor"
      },
      {
          "id": "904",
          "question": "lópez",
          "solution": "lópez",
          "additionText": "lópez"
      },
      {
          "id": "905",
          "question": "victoria",
          "solution": "victory",
          "additionText": "victoria"
      },
      {
          "id": "906",
          "question": "violencia",
          "solution": "violence",
          "additionText": "violence"
      },
      {
          "id": "907",
          "question": "primeras",
          "solution": "first",
          "additionText": "first"
      },
      {
          "id": "908",
          "question": "pequeña",
          "solution": "little",
          "additionText": "small"
      },
      {
          "id": "909",
          "question": "armas",
          "solution": "weapons",
          "additionText": "weapons"
      },
      {
          "id": "910",
          "question": "debía",
          "solution": "should",
          "additionText": "should"
      },
      {
          "id": "911",
          "question": "ii",
          "solution": "ii",
          "additionText": "ii"
      },
      {
          "id": "912",
          "question": "esfuerzo",
          "solution": "effort",
          "additionText": "effort"
      },
      {
          "id": "913",
          "question": "humana",
          "solution": "human",
          "additionText": "human"
      },
      {
          "id": "914",
          "question": "posibilidades",
          "solution": "possibilities",
          "additionText": "possibilities"
      },
      {
          "id": "915",
          "question": "centros",
          "solution": "centers",
          "additionText": "centers"
      },
      {
          "id": "916",
          "question": "profesional",
          "solution": "professional",
          "additionText": "professional"
      },
      {
          "id": "917",
          "question": "asimismo",
          "solution": "in addition",
          "additionText": "also"
      },
      {
          "id": "918",
          "question": "grado",
          "solution": "grade",
          "additionText": "degree"
      },
      {
          "id": "919",
          "question": "has",
          "solution": "you",
          "additionText": "has"
      },
      {
          "id": "920",
          "question": "toma",
          "solution": "taking",
          "additionText": "take"
      },
      {
          "id": "921",
          "question": "distintas",
          "solution": "different",
          "additionText": "different"
      },
      {
          "id": "922",
          "question": "material",
          "solution": "material",
          "additionText": "material"
      },
      {
          "id": "923",
          "question": "carne",
          "solution": "meat",
          "additionText": "meat"
      },
      {
          "id": "924",
          "question": "llama",
          "solution": "call",
          "additionText": "flame"
      },
      {
          "id": "925",
          "question": "particular",
          "solution": "particular",
          "additionText": "particular"
      },
      {
          "id": "926",
          "question": "jorge",
          "solution": "Jorge",
          "additionText": "jorge"
      },
      {
          "id": "927",
          "question": "trabajar",
          "solution": "to work",
          "additionText": "work"
      },
      {
          "id": "928",
          "question": "propuesta",
          "solution": "proposal",
          "additionText": "proposal"
      },
      {
          "id": "929",
          "question": "muerto",
          "solution": "dead",
          "additionText": "dead"
      },
      {
          "id": "930",
          "question": "precios",
          "solution": "prices",
          "additionText": "prices"
      },
      {
          "id": "931",
          "question": "reforma",
          "solution": "reform",
          "additionText": "reform"
      },
      {
          "id": "932",
          "question": "hermano",
          "solution": "brother",
          "additionText": "brother"
      },
      {
          "id": "933",
          "question": "corte",
          "solution": "court",
          "additionText": "court"
      },
      {
          "id": "934",
          "question": "comenzó",
          "solution": "started",
          "additionText": "started"
      },
      {
          "id": "935",
          "question": "etapa",
          "solution": "stage",
          "additionText": "stage"
      },
      {
          "id": "936",
          "question": "obstante",
          "solution": "However",
          "additionText": "however"
      },
      {
          "id": "937",
          "question": "pone",
          "solution": "places",
          "additionText": "put"
      },
      {
          "id": "938",
          "question": "diversos",
          "solution": "different",
          "additionText": "various"
      },
      {
          "id": "939",
          "question": "visita",
          "solution": "visit",
          "additionText": "visit"
      },
      {
          "id": "940",
          "question": "concepto",
          "solution": "concept",
          "additionText": "concept"
      },
      {
          "id": "941",
          "question": "pacientes",
          "solution": "patients",
          "additionText": "patients"
      },
      {
          "id": "942",
          "question": "semanas",
          "solution": "weeks",
          "additionText": "weeks"
      },
      {
          "id": "943",
          "question": "tipos",
          "solution": "types",
          "additionText": "types"
      },
      {
          "id": "944",
          "question": "solamente",
          "solution": "only",
          "additionText": "only"
      },
      {
          "id": "945",
          "question": "deseo",
          "solution": "desire",
          "additionText": "wish"
      },
      {
          "id": "946",
          "question": "sistemas",
          "solution": "systems",
          "additionText": "systems"
      },
      {
          "id": "947",
          "question": "encuentran",
          "solution": "found",
          "additionText": "find"
      },
      {
          "id": "948",
          "question": "siguientes",
          "solution": "following",
          "additionText": "following"
      },
      {
          "id": "949",
          "question": "martín",
          "solution": "Martin",
          "additionText": "martin"
      },
      {
          "id": "950",
          "question": "suficiente",
          "solution": "enough",
          "additionText": "enough"
      },
      {
          "id": "951",
          "question": "marzo",
          "solution": "March",
          "additionText": "March"
      },
      {
          "id": "952",
          "question": "propios",
          "solution": "own",
          "additionText": "own"
      },
      {
          "id": "953",
          "question": "jamás",
          "solution": "Never",
          "additionText": "never"
      },
      {
          "id": "954",
          "question": "dan",
          "solution": "give",
          "additionText": "give"
      },
      {
          "id": "955",
          "question": "club",
          "solution": "club",
          "additionText": "club"
      },
      {
          "id": "956",
          "question": "instituto",
          "solution": "Institute",
          "additionText": "institute"
      },
      {
          "id": "957",
          "question": "constitución",
          "solution": "Constitution",
          "additionText": "constitution"
      },
      {
          "id": "958",
          "question": "curso",
          "solution": "course",
          "additionText": "course"
      },
      {
          "id": "959",
          "question": "lenguaje",
          "solution": "language",
          "additionText": "language"
      },
      {
          "id": "960",
          "question": "estilo",
          "solution": "style",
          "additionText": "style"
      },
      {
          "id": "961",
          "question": "rosa",
          "solution": "rose",
          "additionText": "rose"
      },
      {
          "id": "962",
          "question": "imposible",
          "solution": "impossible",
          "additionText": "impossible"
      },
      {
          "id": "963",
          "question": "pablo",
          "solution": "Pablo",
          "additionText": "pablo"
      },
      {
          "id": "964",
          "question": "buscar",
          "solution": "search",
          "additionText": "search"
      },
      {
          "id": "965",
          "question": "peor",
          "solution": "worse",
          "additionText": "worst"
      },
      {
          "id": "966",
          "question": "piel",
          "solution": "skin",
          "additionText": "skin"
      },
      {
          "id": "967",
          "question": "arriba",
          "solution": "above",
          "additionText": "up"
      },
      {
          "id": "968",
          "question": "generales",
          "solution": "general",
          "additionText": "generals"
      },
      {
          "id": "969",
          "question": "septiembre",
          "solution": "September",
          "additionText": "september"
      },
      {
          "id": "970",
          "question": "blanca",
          "solution": "White",
          "additionText": "white"
      },
      {
          "id": "971",
          "question": "r",
          "solution": "r",
          "additionText": "r"
      },
      {
          "id": "972",
          "question": "aquellas",
          "solution": "those",
          "additionText": "those"
      },
      {
          "id": "973",
          "question": "teoría",
          "solution": "theory",
          "additionText": "theory"
      },
      {
          "id": "974",
          "question": "animales",
          "solution": "animals",
          "additionText": "animals"
      },
      {
          "id": "975",
          "question": "hicieron",
          "solution": "they made",
          "additionText": "made"
      },
      {
          "id": "976",
          "question": "larga",
          "solution": "long",
          "additionText": "long"
      },
      {
          "id": "977",
          "question": "perdido",
          "solution": "lost",
          "additionText": "lost"
      },
      {
          "id": "978",
          "question": "imágenes",
          "solution": "images",
          "additionText": "images"
      },
      {
          "id": "979",
          "question": "paciente",
          "solution": "patient",
          "additionText": "patient"
      },
      {
          "id": "980",
          "question": "conseguir",
          "solution": "to get",
          "additionText": "get"
      },
      {
          "id": "981",
          "question": "máximo",
          "solution": "maximum",
          "additionText": "maximum"
      },
      {
          "id": "982",
          "question": "noviembre",
          "solution": "November",
          "additionText": "November"
      },
      {
          "id": "983",
          "question": "j",
          "solution": "j",
          "additionText": "j"
      },
      {
          "id": "984",
          "question": "líder",
          "solution": "Leader",
          "additionText": "leader"
      },
      {
          "id": "985",
          "question": "hospital",
          "solution": "hospital",
          "additionText": "hospital"
      },
      {
          "id": "986",
          "question": "diversas",
          "solution": "different",
          "additionText": "various"
      },
      {
          "id": "987",
          "question": "rafael",
          "solution": "rafael",
          "additionText": "rafael"
      },
      {
          "id": "988",
          "question": "vuelve",
          "solution": "returns",
          "additionText": "return"
      },
      {
          "id": "989",
          "question": "destino",
          "solution": "destination",
          "additionText": "destination"
      },
      {
          "id": "990",
          "question": "torno",
          "solution": "turnstile",
          "additionText": "lathe"
      },
      {
          "id": "991",
          "question": "proyectos",
          "solution": "Projects",
          "additionText": "projects"
      },
      {
          "id": "992",
          "question": "flores",
          "solution": "flowers",
          "additionText": "flowers"
      },
      {
          "id": "993",
          "question": "niveles",
          "solution": "levels",
          "additionText": "levels"
      },
      {
          "id": "994",
          "question": "afirmó",
          "solution": "he claimed",
          "additionText": "stated"
      },
      {
          "id": "995",
          "question": "explicó",
          "solution": "he explained",
          "additionText": "explained"
      },
      {
          "id": "996",
          "question": "n",
          "solution": "n",
          "additionText": "n"
      },
      {
          "id": "997",
          "question": "somos",
          "solution": "are",
          "additionText": "we are"
      },
      {
          "id": "998",
          "question": "términos",
          "solution": "Terms",
          "additionText": "terms"
      },
      {
          "id": "999",
          "question": "premio",
          "solution": "prize",
          "additionText": "award"
      },
      {
          "id": "1000",
          "question": "tercera",
          "solution": "third",
          "additionText": "third"
      }
  ]
}
